(window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[]).push([["english-mobile-new"],{"11e9":function(e,t,o){var n=o("52a7"),a=o("4630"),s=o("6821"),i=o("6a99"),r=o("69a8"),h=o("c69a"),l=Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor;t.f=o("9e1e")?l:function(e,t){if(e=s(e),t=i(t,!0),h)try{return l(e,t)}catch(o){}if(r(e,t))return a(!n.f.call(e,t),e[t])}},"154f":function(e,t,o){},"1af6":function(e,t,o){var n=o("63b6");n(n.S,"Array",{isArray:o("9003")})},"20fd":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("d9f6"),a=o("aebd");e.exports=function(e,t,o){t in e?n.f(e,t,a(0,o)):e[t]=o}},"335f":function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);var n=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",{staticClass:"home"},[o("van-nav-bar",{staticStyle:{"border-bottom":"1px solid #efefef"},attrs:{title:"英语","left-arrow":"",fixed:""},on:{"click-left":function(t){return e.$router.push("/mobile")}}}),o("div",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.submit,expression:"submit"}],staticClass:"score"},[e._v(e._s(e.score)+" 分")]),o("div",{staticStyle:{width:"100%",height:"50px"}}),o("div",{staticClass:"dx"},e._l(e.dxlist,function(t,n){return o("dl",{key:n},[o("div",{staticClass:"question"},[o("div",{staticClass:"no"},[e._v(e._s(n+1)+".")]),o("div",{staticClass:"text",domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.question.replace(/\n/g,"<br/>"))}}),o("span",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.submit,expression:"submit"}],staticClass:"answer",style:{color:t.xx===t.answer?"green":"red"}},[e._v("\n          "+e._s(t.answer)+"\n        ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"options"},[o("van-radio-group",{model:{value:t.xx,callback:function(o){e.$set(t,"xx",o)},expression:"item.xx"}},e._l(t.options,function(t,n){return o("van-radio",{key:t,attrs:{name:e.A_Z[n]}},[e._v(e._s(e.A_Z[n])+"."+e._s(t))])}),1)],1)])}),0),o("div",{staticClass:"wx"},e._l(e.wxlist,function(t,n){return o("dl",{key:n},[o("div",{staticClass:"wz"},[o("div",{staticClass:"no"},[e._v(e._s(n+1+e.dxlist.length)+".")]),o("div",{staticClass:"text",domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.text.replace(/\n/g,"<br/>"))}})]),o("div",{staticClass:"questions"},e._l(t.questions,function(t,a){return o("div",{key:"question"+n+"-"+a,staticClass:"question"},[o("div",{staticClass:"no"},[e._v(e._s(a+1)+".")]),o("div",{staticClass:"options"},[o("van-radio-group",{model:{value:t.xx,callback:function(o){e.$set(t,"xx",o)},expression:"question.xx"}},e._l(t.options,function(t,n){return o("van-radio",{key:t,attrs:{name:e.A_Z[n]}},[e._v(e._s(e.A_Z[n])+"."+e._s(t))])}),1)],1),o("span",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.submit,expression:"submit"}],staticClass:"answer",style:{color:t.xx===t.answer?"green":"red"}},[e._v("\n            "+e._s(t.answer)+"\n          ")])])}),0)])}),0),o("div",{staticClass:"yd"},e._l(e.ydlist,function(t,n){return o("dl",{key:n},[o("div",{staticClass:"wz"},[o("div",{staticClass:"no"},[e._v(e._s(n+1+e.dxlist.length+e.wxlist.length)+".")]),o("div",{staticClass:"text",domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.text.replace(/\n/g,"<br/>"))}})]),o("div",{staticClass:"questions"},e._l(t.questions,function(t,a){return o("dl",{key:"question"+n+"-"+a},[o("div",{staticClass:"question"},[o("div",{staticClass:"no"},[e._v(e._s(a+1)+".")]),o("div",{staticClass:"text",domProps:{innerHTML:e._s(t.question.replace(/\n/g,"<br/>"))}}),o("span",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.submit,expression:"submit"}],staticClass:"answer",style:{color:t.xx===t.answer?"green":"red"}},[e._v("\n              "+e._s(t.answer)+"\n            ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"options"},[o("van-radio-group",{model:{value:t.xx,callback:function(o){e.$set(t,"xx",o)},expression:"question.xx"}},e._l(t.options,function(t,n){return o("van-radio",{key:t,attrs:{name:e.A_Z[n]}},[e._v("\n                "+e._s(e.A_Z[n])+"."+e._s(t)+"\n              ")])}),1)],1)])}),0)])}),0),o("div",{staticStyle:{height:"50px",widht:"100%"}}),o("van-goods-action",[o("van-goods-action-button",{attrs:{type:"info",text:"提交"},on:{click:e.submitFn}}),o("van-goods-action-button",{attrs:{type:"danger",text:"重来"},on:{click:e.reset}})],1)],1)},a=[],s=(o("8e6e"),o("456d"),o("a481"),o("ac6a"),o("bd86")),i=o("75fc"),r=[{question:"-How about going to dinner at the Mexican restaurant tonigh?\n- \t_\t",options:["Forget it.\t","Sorry, I like Mexican food.\t","That's great!\t","Glad you like it."],answer:"C"},{question:"-Shall we sit up here on the grass or down there near the water?\n- \t",options:["I'd rather stay here if you don't mind.\t","Sorry, I don't like neither.","Certainly, why not?\t","Yes, we like these two places."],answer:"A"},{question:"-Is it possible for you to work late tonight?\t\n- \t_.",options:["I like it\t","I'll do that\t","I'd love to\t","I think so"],answer:"D"},{question:"-Must I take a taxi?  \n-No, you \t. You can take a car.",options:["had better to","don't","must not\t","don't have to"],answer:"D"},{question:"-Would you mind changing seats with me?\n- \t.",options:["Yes, you can\t","Of course, I like to\t","No, I don't mind\t","Certainly, please do"],answer:"C"},{question:"-Wow!This is a marvelous room! I've never known you're so artistic.\t- \t.",options:["Great, I am very art-conscious\t","Don't mention it","Thanks for your compliments\t","It's fine"],answer:"C"},{question:"-  \t?\t\n-Well, they got there last Wednesday. So about a week. ",options:["When did your parents arrive at Paris\t","How long have your parents been in Paris","Did your parents arrive at Paris last Wednesday\t","When will your parents go to Paris"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Could I borrow your car for a few day?\n- \t_.",options:["Yes, you may borrow\t","Yes, go on","Sure, here you are. Enjoy your journey\t","It doesn't matter"],answer:"C"},{question:"-Congratulations!You won the first prize in today's speech contest. - \t.",options:["Yes, I beat the others\t","No, no, I didn't do it well\t","Thank you\t","It's pleasure"],answer:"C"},{question:"-Hi,Tom, how's everything with you?  \n- \t, and how are you?\t",options:["Don't mention it      ","Hm, not too bad         ","Thanks            ","Pretty fast"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Excuse me, could you show me the way to the nearest post office?\n-  \tOh yes! Two blocks away from here at the Green Avenue. You can't miss it.",options:["I beg your pardon?\t","What do you mean?\t","You're welcome.\t","Mm, let me think."],answer:"D"},{question:"--Unbelievable! I have failed the driving test again!\n-- \t. This is not the end of the world.  ",options:[" Good luck\t","Cheer up\t","Go ahead\t","No problem"],answer:"B"},{question:"--Could you help me with my physics, please?\n-- \t .",options:[" No, no way\t","No, I couldn't","No, I can't\t","Sorry I can't. I have to go to a meeting right now"],answer:"D"},{question:"—Haven't seen you for ages! What are you busy doing now?\n-- \t .",options:[" I have the weather here\t","My hair is getting a bit longer","Yeah, thanks for coming\t","I am working part time in a bookshop, you know"],answer:"D"},{question:"—How do you do? Glad to meet you.\n-- \t.",options:[" Fine. How are you?\t","How do you do? Glad to meet you, too.","How are you? Thank you!\t","Nice. How are you? "],answer:"B"},{question:"—Who's that speaking?/ Who's speaking?\n--This is Tom   \t .",options:["speaks\t","spoken\t","speaking\t","saying"],answer:"C"},{question:"—How are you, Bob?\n--   \t, ",options:["How are you?     ","I'm fine. Thank you.   ","How do you do?\t","Nice to meet you."],answer:"B"},{question:"-Paul, \t?\n-Oh, that's my father! And beside him, my mother.",options:[" what is the person over there.\t"," who's talking over there."," what are they doing.\t"," which is that."],answer:"B"},{question:"-How often do you go dancing?\n- \t_.\t",options:["I will go dancing tomorrow.\t"," Yesterday."," Every other day.\t"," I've been dancing for a year."],answer:"C"},{question:"-Hello, may I talk to the director now?\n- \t.",options:[" Sorry, he is busy at the moment.\t"," No, you can't. "," Sorry, you can't.\t","I don't know."],answer:"A"},{question:"--I'm sorry. I lost the key.\n-- \t.",options:[" Well, it's OK\t"," No, it's all right\t"," You are welcome\t"," You are wrong"],answer:"A"},{question:"-- \t_?\n--He teaches physics in a school.",options:[" what does your father want to do\t"," who is your father"," what is your father\t"," where is your father now"],answer:"C"},{question:"-How was your trip to London, Jane?\n- \t.",options:[" Oh, wonderful indeed\t","I went there alone"," The guide showed me the way\t"," By plane and by bus"],answer:"A"},{question:"-Thank you for inviting me.\n- \t",options:["I really had a happy time.\t"," Oh, it's too late. "," Thank you for coming.\t"," Oh, so slowly"],answer:"C"},{question:"-May I see your tickets, please?\n- \t.",options:[" No, they are mine\t"," No, you can't\t"," Sure\t"," Yes, you can"],answer:"C"},{question:"--Please help yourself to the seafood.\n- \t_.",options:[" No, I can't.\t"," Sorry, I can't help"," well, seafood don't suit for\t"," Thanks, but I don't like the seafood"],answer:"D"},{question:"-Hey, Tom, what's up?\n- \t_.",options:[" Yes, definitely!\t"," Oh, not much. "," What is happening in your life?\t"," You are lucky."],answer:"B"},{question:"-Do you mind my smoking here?\n- \t.",options:[" No, thanks   "," Yes, I do\t"," Yes, I'd rather not\t"," Good idea"],answer:"B"},{question:"-I wonder if I could use your computer tonight?\n- \tI'm not using it right now.",options:[" Sure, go ahead.\t","I don't know.\t"," It doesn't matter.\t"," Who cares?"],answer:"A"},{question:"-We are going to have a singing party tonight. Would you like to join us?\n- \t_.",options:["I'm afraid not, because I have to go to an important meeting","Of course not. I have no idea","No, I can't","That's all set"],answer:"A"},{question:"—Why didn't you come to my birthday party yesterday?\t \t.",options:["Excuse me, my friend sent me a flower\t","Fine, I never go to birthday parties","Well, I don't like birthday parties\t","Sorry, but my wife had a car accident"],answer:"D"},{question:"—This box is too heavy for me to carry upstairs.\t\n-- \t--",options:["You may ask for help\t","I'll give you a hand","Please do me a favor\t","I'd come to help"],answer:"B"},{question:" -That's a beautiful dress you have on!  \n-  \t.",options:["Oh, thanks. I got it yesterday\t","Sorry, it's too cheap\t","You can have it\t","See you later"],answer:"A"},{question:" -David injured his leg playing football yesterday. \n-Really?  \t",options:["Who did that","What's wrong with him","How did that happen","Why was he so careless"],answer:"C"},{question:" -Hi, is Mary there, please?-  \t",options:["Hold on. I'll get her.\t\t","No, she isn't here.","Yes, she lives here.\t","Yes, what do you want?"],answer:"A"},{question:"\t-It's rather cold in here. Do you mind if I close the window? -  \t_.",options:["Yes, please\t","No, go ahead\t","Sure, please\t","I don't like it"],answer:"B"},{question:" -Medam,do all the buses go downtown?\n-  \t.\t",options:["Wow, you got the idea\t","No, never mind","pretty well, I guess\t","Sorry, I'm new here"],answer:"D"},{question:" -Could I speak to Don Watkins, please? \n-  \t\t",options:["I'm listening.\t","Oh, how are you?\t"," Speaking, please.\t","I'm Don."],answer:"C"},{question:" -Thanks for your help.\t-  \t.",options:["My pleasure\t","Never mind\t","Quite right\t","Don't thank me"],answer:"A"},{question:"-Hello, I'm Harry Potter. \n-Hello, my name is Charles Green, but  \t. ",options:["call my Charles\t","call me at Charles\t","call me Charles\t","call Charles me"],answer:"C"},{question:"-Can you go to the concert with us this evening?\t\n- \t.\t",options:["No, I already have plans                                     ","I'd love to, but I'm busy tonight","No, I really don't like being with you                 ","I'm will, so I shouldn't go out"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Marilyn, I'm afraid I have to be leaving now.\n- \t",options:["That sounds wonderful.          ","Oh, so early?\t","Not at all.\t","Good luck!"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Hi, welcome back! Had a nice trip?\n-________",options:[" Oh, fantastic! Fresh air, and sunshine every day. "," Come on, I've got lots of fun."," By the way, I don't like Saturdays."," Well, I'll look forward to your phone call."],answer:"A"},{question:"-Excuse me, how much is the jacket?\t\n-It's 499 Yuan._____.\t",options:[" Oh, no. That's OK!\t"," How do you like it?\t"," Which do you prefer?"," Would you like to try it on?"],answer:"D"},{question:" — May I use your bike for a moment?\n-_____",options:[" It's well.\t"," It doesn't matter.\t"," By all means.\t"," I have no idea."],answer:"C"},{question:"- I'm sorry. I am late due to heavy traffic. \n-  \t.\t",options:["Well,  it's  OK.     \t"," No, it's all right. \t"," You are welcome.          "," You are wrong."],answer:"A"},{question:" - Are you feeling better today, Jack.  \n-  \t  .                   ",options:[" There must be something wrong.","  Just have a good rest."," Yes, thank you, doctor. But I still don't feel good."," Don't worry about me."],answer:"C"},{question:" Would you like something to drink? What about a cup of tea?  \n-  \t.                  ",options:["  No, thanks.         "," No, I wouldn't          "," Yes, I want.         "," Yes, I like."],answer:"A"},{question:" –Good morning, John. How are you doing?  \n-  \t.         ",options:[" I  am pleased.             "," Good night.               "," Not so bad. And you?              "," How do you do? "],answer:"C"},{question:"- How do you do?        \n-  \t.       ",options:[" Fine,thank you.     "," How do you do?        "," Not too bad.         "," Very well. "],answer:"B"},{question:" –Thank you for your invitation.      \n-  \t.                             ",options:[" It doesn't matter        "," It's pleasure.            "," It's a small thing.         "," I'll appreciate it. "],answer:"B"},{question:" – Let me introduce myself. I'm Steward.      \n-  \t.               ",options:["What a pleasure.       ","  Pleased to meet you.          "," I don't know.            "," Thanks a lot.  "],answer:"B"},{question:" Let's go to the library this afternoon.        \n-  \t.                           ",options:[" Yes, that's right.             "," No, I can't.                "," What about you?               "," That's a good idea."],answer:"D"},{question:" –How tall is your sister?            \n-  \t.                     ",options:["She is not very tall.          "," She is 28 years old.          "," She is very nice.           "," She is as tall as I am."],answer:"D"},{question:"- What  do you think of this novel?       \n-  \t.                      ",options:["I've read it.        "," It's well-written.         "," It's was written by my uncle        "," I bought it yesterday."],answer:"B"},{question:" –How much is this necklace?      \n-  \t.          ",options:["It's very nice.                         "," It's a birthday present from my parents.   "," It costs fifty pounds.               "," It's a bargain. "],answer:"C"},{question:"- How can I get to the cinema?      \n-  \t.                    ",options:["It's very far.                 "," Yes, there is cinema near here. "," It's well known.             "," Go down this street and turn left. "],answer:"D"},{question:"- what's the matter John?       \n-  \t.             ",options:["I failed my French test.                    "," It doesn't matter.   ","  Nothing's wrong with him.             ","  I don't think I can."],answer:"A"},{question:" – What are you majoring in?         \n-  \t.                     ",options:[" In a university.            "," Very hard.          "," Mathematics.          "," At nine in the morning.  "],answer:"C"},{question:" – Is Mary there?       \n-  \t.         ",options:["Speaking.                ","I'm not Mary.                ","Who are you?           ","Mary is well today? "],answer:"A"},{question:"- What day is today?         \n-  \t.              ",options:["It's  March 6、                  "," It's a fine day today.           "," It's  March                "," It's Monday."],answer:"D"},{question:" – It's that seat taken?     \n-  \t.             ",options:["Please don't worry.        "," I don't think so.          "," Why not?             "," It's very nice. "],answer:"B"},{question:"- Thank you for calling.           \n-  \t.                     ",options:["Don't mention it.             "," That's fine.            "," Nice talking to you.          "," Call back again.  "],answer:"C"},{question:"- How are you getting on today?                \n-  \t.               ",options:[" Very well.             "," How do you do?           "," I am a doctor?                "," Nice to have known you. "],answer:"A"},{question:"- How's is your family?               \n-  \t.                        ",options:["Thanks all the same.               "," Thanks for calling.           "," Not too bad.           "," Don't mention it.  "],answer:"C"},{question:" –Would you like to go to the concert with us this evening?      \n-  \t.                            ",options:[" No, I already have plans.                  "," I'd love to , but  I'm busy tonight. "," No, I really don't like being with you.              "," I'm ill, so I shouldn't go out. "],answer:"B"},{question:" – Thank you so much for the coat you bought me.      \n-  \t.            ",options:[" No thanks.          ",". I'm glad you like it.          "," Please don't say so.            "," No, it's not so good. "],answer:"B"},{question:"-What's the problem with your bike?          \n-  \t.                     ",options:[" Not at all.                  "," Good, thank you.            "," Nothing serious.                 "," Sure"],answer:"C"},{question:" –Good-bye for now.      \n-  \t.             ",options:[" The same to you.            "," That's Ok.               "," See you.                  "," Long time no see. "],answer:"C"},{question:" – Hello, how are you?             \n-  \t.           ",options:["Hello, how are you?           "," How do you do ?            "," Fine, thank you.               "," That's OK."],answer:"C"},{question:"- I  didn't mean to do that. Please forgive me.       \n-  \t.                    ",options:["Not to bad.            "," That's all right.           "," It's pleasure.              ","  Thank you "],answer:"B"},{question:"- What a beautiful dress you have on today!      \n-  \t.               ",options:["It is suitable for me.         "," No, it isn't.         "," You want to have one, too?        "," Thank you "],answer:"D"},{question:"- I think he is a good lecturer.          \n-  \t.                ",options:[" Sorry, it doesn't matter.     "," So do I.          "," Yes, it's a good idea.        "," I don't mind. "],answer:"B"},{question:"- What's the matter, dear?      \n-  \t.   ",options:[" I  didn't go to school.                           "," I have a terrible headache. "," I took the kids shopping today.               "," It is a beautiful dress. "],answer:"B"},{question:"-Good morning,  may I speak to Mark, please?        \n-  \t.       ",options:["Who's there?        "," Who's speaking?           "," Who are you?               "," Who wants to speak to Mark? "],answer:"B"},{question:"- Are you going on holiday for long time?      \n-  \t.          ",options:[" It was a long time.      "," Two weeks ago.        "," No, only a couple of days.      "," Not long time ago."],answer:"C"},{question:"- What does Tom's wife do for a living?             \n-  \t.         ",options:["She is a doctor.                   "," Tom loves his wife.         "," She has a happy life.          "," She  lives far from here.  "],answer:"A"},{question:"- I believe we've met somewhere before.\n- NO,  \t.                 ",options:[" It isn't the same.         "," It can't be right.          "," I don't think so.          "," I'd rather not. "],answer:"C"},{question:"- Hello, could I speak to Mr. Smith, please?      \n-  \t.             ",options:[" Who are you?             "," Who's there?             "," Who could I help?           "," who's that speaking? "],answer:"D"},{question:"-Let me introduce myself. I am Tom.   \n-  \t.          ",options:[" What a pleasure.         "," It's pleasure.           "," I'm very pleased.             ","   Pleased to meet you"],answer:"D"},{question:" –I have passed the English exam.       \n-  \t.  Congratulations.     ",options:["Sorry                  "," Good luck.                  ","  Come on.                 "," Well done. "],answer:"D"},{question:"-I am sorry. Bod is not in his office.   \n-  \t?   ",options:[" Can you take a message for me?               "," Are you sure for that?"," Would you like to leave a message?            "," Can you phone me- I haven't seen Belly for 10 years? "],answer:"A"},{question:" –Could you pass me the salt and pepper?   \n-  \t.   ",options:["Sorry, I didn't know what you mean.      "," Ok, here you are.       "," No, I won't.         "," I don't know. "],answer:"B"},{question:"- I'd like to book a room, please.                       \n-  \t.                        ",options:[" Single or double?        "," Good or bad?          "," Which room?              "," We don't have books here. "],answer:"A"},{question:" – Thank you for your nice gift.               \n-  \t.                     ",options:[" I'd glad you like it.         "," No thanks.           "," It's very kind of you.          "," I'm sorry to hear that.  "],answer:"A"},{question:"-Is it ok if I take this seat?        \n- Sorry,  \t                 .       ",options:[" Here you are            "," take it.             "," It's taken              "," never mind. "],answer:"C"},{question:"- I really don't know how to thank you enough.         \n-  \t                 .              ",options:["No problem.        "," Think nothing of it.       "," Not at all.          "," It doesn't matter"],answer:"B"},{question:"- Happy Teachers' Day to you. Mr Wang!     \n-  \t                 . ",options:[" Thank you                "," All the same.               "," Me, too.          "," The same to you. "],answer:"A"},{question:"- Can I help you?   \n-  \t                ",options:[" Ok, I'll take it.             ","  That's good.          "," Yes, I'd like a answer.           "," It's too dear.  "],answer:"C"},{question:" May I use your dictionary?    \n-  \t                 .    ",options:["Yes, here you are.              "," No, you won't              "," Never mind.           ","Sorry here it is."],answer:"A"}],h=[{question:"I have been looking forward to                 from my parents. ",options:["hear\t","being heared\t","be heared\t","hearing"],answer:"D"},{question:"The manager will not                 us to use his car. ",options:["have\t","let\t","agree\t","allow"],answer:"D"},{question:"               Her and then try to copy what she does．",options:["Mind\t","See\t","Stare at\t","Watch"],answer:"D"},{question:"Will you                  me a favor, please? ",options:["do\t","make\t","bring\t","give"],answer:"A"},{question:"It's bad                  for you to smoke in the public places where smoking is not allowed．",options:["behavior          ","action          ","manner\t","movement"],answer:"A"},{question:"-it's a good idea. But who's going to                  the plan? \n- I think John and Peter will.  ",options:["carry out\t","get through\t","take in\t\t","set aside"],answer:"A"},{question:"The computer system                 suddenly while he was searching for information on the Internet.  ",options:["broke down\t","broke out\t","broke up\t","broke in"],answer:"A"},{question:"If she wants to stay thin, she must make a                 in her diet. ",options:["change\t","turn\t\t","run\t","go"],answer:"A"},{question:"                theWar of Independence, the United States was an England colony.  ",options:["Before\t","At                 ","In                     ","Between"],answer:"A"},{question:"A police officer claimed that he had attempted to                  paying his fare. ",options:["avoid\t","reject\t","refuse\t","neglect"],answer:"A"},{question:"Mike is better than Peter                 swimming． ",options:["for\t","at\t","on\t","in"],answer:"B"},{question:"The young lady coming over to us                 our English teacher; the way she walks tell us that! ",options:["must be\t","can be\t","would be\t","could be"],answer:"A"},{question:"Eggs, though rich in nourishments, have                 of fat.",options:["a large number of       ","the large number       "," a large amount  \t","the large amount"],answer:"C"},{question:"Neither John                 his father was able to wake up early enough to catch the morning train． ",options:["nor\t","or\t","but\t","and"],answer:"A"},{question:"Jane's dress is similar in design                 her sister's.",options:["like\t","with\t","to\t","as"],answer:"C"},{question:"His salary as a driver is much higher than                 ． ",options:["a porter\t","is a porter\t","as a porter\t","that of porter"],answer:"D"},{question:"-Write to me when you get home.\n-OK,I                . ",options:["must\t"," should \t","will \t","can"],answer:"C"},{question:"Tom is talkative. I'm sure you'll soon get tired                 him. ",options:["of\t","with\t","at\t","on"],answer:"A"},{question:"I don't know                  to deal with such matter. ",options:["what\t","how\t","which\t","/"],answer:"B"},{question:"-is your girl friend like?   \n-She is very kind and good-looking.  ",options:["How\t","What\t","Which\t","Who"],answer:"B"},{question:"He                 driving me home, even though I told him I lived nearby． ",options:["insisted on\t","insisted at\t","insisted that\t","insisted in"],answer:"A"},{question:"We came finally                  the conclusion that she has been telling lies all the time．",options:["of\t","into\t","to\t","at"],answer:"C"},{question:"I won't make the                 mistake next time. ",options:["like\t","same\t","near\t","similar"],answer:"B"},{question:"He                  lives in the house where he was born. ",options:["already\t   ","yet\t","still\t","ever"],answer:"C"},{question:"I am not used to speaking                 public.",options:["in\t","at\t","on\t","to"],answer:"A"},{question:"I didn't know what to do, but then an idea suddenly                 to me． ",options:["appeared\t","happened\t","occurred\t","emerged"],answer:"C"},{question:"A pair of spectacles                 what I need at the moment．",options:["is\t","are\t","has\t","have"],answer:"A"},{question:"You'd better                  a doctor as soon as possible．",options:["seeing\t","saw\t","see\t","seen"],answer:"C"},{question:"                These honors he received a sun of money．",options:["Except\t","But\t","Besides\t","Outside"],answer:"C"},{question:"Would you let                 to the park with my classmate, Mum? ",options:["me go\t","me going    ","I go\t","I going"],answer:"A"},{question:"Neither Bill or his parents \t\tat home.  ",options:["is\t","has\t","are\t","was"],answer:"C"},{question:"If you don't want to get wet, you had better \tthis umbrella with you.  ",options:["take\t","to take\t","taken\t","for taking"],answer:"A"},{question:"Measles                 a long time to get over.   ",options:["spend\t","spends\t","take\t","takes"],answer:"D"},{question:"-Do you want to wait? 您愿意等吗?\n-Five days \t          too long for me to wait.  ",options:[" was\t","were\t","is\t","are"],answer:"C"},{question:"There                a book and some magazines on the desk. ",options:["is\t","are\t","have\t","has "],answer:"A"},{question:"She is not only my classmate                also my good friend. ",options:["or\t","but\t","and\t","too"],answer:"B"},{question:"He asked the waiter                the bill.  ",options:["on\t","of\t","for\t","after"],answer:"C"},{question:"When Lily came home at 5 p.m. yesterday, her mother                 dinner in the kichen.",options:["cooked\t","was cooking\t","cooks\t","has cooked"],answer:"B"},{question:"Di you noticed the guy                 head looked like a big potato? ",options:["who\t","which\t","whose\t","whom"],answer:"C"},{question:"I don't know the park, but it's                 to be quite beautiful. ",options:["said                 ","old                     ","spoken           ","talked   "],answer:"A"},{question:"While I was in the university, I learned taking a photo,                 is very useful now for me.  ",options:["it\t","which\t","that\t"," what"],answer:"B"},{question:"On average, a successful lawyer has to talk to several                  a day. ",options:["customers\t","supporters\t","guests\t","clients"],answer:"D"},{question:"What is the train                 to Birmingham?  ",options:["fee\t","tip\t","fare\t","cost"],answer:"C"},{question:" You shouldn't                 your time like that, Bob. You have to finish your school work tonight.     ",options:["cut\t","do\t","kill\t","kick"],answer:"C"},{question:"Both the kids and their parents  \t\tEnglish, I think. I know it from their accent. ",options:["is\t","been\t","are\t","Was "],answer:"C"},{question:"I tried to put                a telephone call to him, but his line was always bus.",options:["over\t","into\t","away\t"," through"],answer:"D"},{question:"I hadn't seen him for years, but I                his voice on the telephone.  ",options:["realized\t","recognized\t","discovered\t","heard"],answer:"B"},{question:"She wonders                will happen to her private life in the future.  ",options:["that\t","it\t","this\t","what"],answer:"D"},{question:" The higher the temperature,                the liquid evaporates.  ",options:["the faster\t","the most fast\t","the slower\t","the more slower"],answer:"A"},{question:"Australia is one of the few countries                 people drive on the left of the road.",options:["which\t","that\t","where\t","on which"],answer:"C"},{question:"Sunday is the day                people usually don't go to work. ",options:["when\t","which\t","in which\t"," on which"],answer:"A"},{question:"               you know,David has been well lately. ",options:["Which \t","As\t","What\t","When"],answer:"B"},{question:"The harder you study,                you will learn.  ",options:["That      ","It     ","the  more      ","what"],answer:"C"},{question:" They got here an hour                 than the others. ",options:["early\t","much early\t","more early\t","earlier"],answer:"D"},{question:"The grey building is the place where the workers live, and the white building is the place where the spare parts                .",options:["are producing\t","are produced\t","produced\t","being produced"],answer:"B"},{question:"Professor smith promised to look                my paper, that is, to read it carefully before the defence.  ",options:["after\t","over\t","on\t","into"],answer:"B"},{question:"Our house is about a mile from the railway station and there are not many houses               .  ",options:["in between\t","far apart\t","among them\t","from each other"],answer:"A"},{question:"As the bus came around the corner, it ran                 a big tree by the roadside. ",options:["into\t","on\t","over\t","up"],answer:"A"},{question:"Had you come five minutes earlier, you                the train to Birmingham. But now you missed it. ",options:[" would catch\t","would have caught\t","could catch\t","should catch"],answer:"B"},{question:"Never before               see such a terrible car accident on the road.",options:["I have\t","have I\t","I did\t","did I"],answer:"D"},{question:"This kind of material expands                 the temperature increasing. ",options:["to\t","for\t","with\t","at"],answer:"C"},{question:"People at the party worried about him because no one was aware                 he had gone.  ",options:["of where\t","of the place where             ","where \t","the place"],answer:"A"},{question:"A sudden noise of a fire-engine made him                 to the door. ",options:["hurrying\t","hurried\t","hurry\t","to hurry"],answer:"C"},{question:"No matter                , the little sisters managed to round the sheep up and drive them back home safely. ",options:["it was snowing hard                                                   ","hard it was snowing\t","how it was snowing hard\t","how hard it was snowing"],answer:"D"},{question:"There's lots of fruit                 the tree. Our little cat is also in the tree. ",options:["in               ","at                  ","under           ","On  "],answer:"D"},{question:"How can be                 if he is not                ?  ",options:["listen; hearing                        ","hear; listening \t","be listening;  heard                ","be hearing; listened to"],answer:"B"},{question:"The students were all entertained in a Mexican restaurant, at Professor Brian's                  .  ",options:["money\t","pay\t","expense\t","loss"],answer:"C"},{question:"Tom what did you do with my documents? I have never seen such a                 and disorder.  ",options:["mass\t","mess\t","guess\t","bus"],answer:"B"},{question:"The atmosphere                 certain gases mixed together in definite proportions.",options:[" composes of      ","is made up\t","consists of\t","makes up of"],answer:"C"},{question:"The girl is                 of a film star. ",options:["somebody\t","something\t","anybody\t","anyone"],answer:"B"},{question:"It's time we                 the lecture because everybody has arrived. ",options:["will start\t","shall start\t","start\t","started"],answer:"D"},{question:"Therefore, other things                 equal, the member of workers that employers want decreases.  ",options:["is\t","are          ","being \t","having"],answer:"C"},{question:"Two days is not enough for him to finish the work. He needs                 day. ",options:["other\t","the other\t","the third\t","a third"],answer:"D"},{question:"The red flower goes from one to                in the class. ",options:["the other                      ","others \t","another\t","other"],answer:"C"},{question:"Once environmental damage               , it takes many years for the system to recover. ",options:["is to do               ","does                  ","had done           ","is done "],answer:"D"},{question:"We worked hard and completed the task               . ",options:["in the time               ","on the time                  ","ahead of time          ","before time."],answer:"C"},{question:" I didn't expect you to turn               at the meeting yesterday. ",options:["up              ","to                ","out           ","over "],answer:"A"},{question:"I'd like the teacher                classes are very interesting and creative. ",options:["which                ","who                 ","whose          ","what"],answer:"C"},{question:"-He is not seriously ill, only a               headache. ",options:["obvious              ","delicate                  ","slight           ","temporary"],answer:"C"},{question:"The boy is not happy at the new school. He has              friends there.  ",options:["few                ","a few                  ","little           ","a littl"],answer:"A"},{question:"I fell and hurt myself while I                basketball yesterday.",options:["was playing                ","am playing                 ","play           ","played "],answer:"A"},{question:"Tom                more than twenty pounds on the novel. ",options:["spent                ","paid                  ","cost          ","took "],answer:"A"},{question:"Don't forget               the window before leaving the room. ",options:["to have closed               ","to close                 ","having closed           ","closing "],answer:"B"},{question:"Twenty people were               wounded in the air crash. ",options:["quickly                ","wrongly                 ","bitterly           "," seriously "],answer:"D"},{question:"The top of the Great Wall is                for five horses to go side by side. ",options:["wide               ","so wide                 ","wide enough           ","enough wide"],answer:"C"},{question:"We have missed the last bus, I'm afraid we have no               but to take taxi. ",options:["way               ","choice                 ","possibility          ","selection "],answer:"B"},{question:"Nancy is considered to be                the other students in her class. ",options:["less intelligent               ","the most intelligent                 ","intelligent as well                  ","as intelligent as "],answer:"D"},{question:"It's                that he was wrong. ",options:["clearly               ","clarity                 ","clear         ","clearing"],answer:"C"},{question:"               you are leaving tomorrow, we can have dinner together tonight.",options:["Since               ","While                 ","For          ","Before"],answer:"A"},{question:"I would like to do the job               you don't force me to study. ",options:["in case               ","although                 ","though          ","as long as"],answer:"D"},{question:"The reason I did not go abroad was                a job in my home town. ",options:["because              ","due to                 ","that I got          ","because of getting"],answer:"C"},{question:"               She survived the accident is miracle.   ",options:["What              ","That                 ","As          ","Which"],answer:"B"},{question:"I often see               the road on his way home. ",options:["he cross              ","him cross                 ","him crossed         ","he crossing"],answer:"B"},{question:"His mother               alone since his father died. ",options:["lived               ","lives                ","has lived          ","is living"],answer:"C"},{question:"The workers are busy                models for the exhibition. ",options:["to make               ","with making                 ","being making         ","making"],answer:"D"},{question:"It was well known that Thomas Edison               the electric lamp. ",options:["discovered               ","invented                ","found          ","developed"],answer:"B"}],l=[{text:"Morgan Rees has always been a good businessman. He used to own three petrol stations and was busy most of the time. When he was 65, the normal retirement age, he decided that the didn't want to stop, so he carried on working for another two years. Eventually, when he was nearly 68, his wiefe, Dolly, asked him to retire because she wanted to enjoy their old age together. Reluctantaly, he handed over the business to his son.\nBut he was unhappy. He didn't know what to do with himself. Although he read a lot of books and he went on holiday to interesting places with his wife, he was bored and befgan to get deperessed because he hated being retired.\nThen one day he saw an advertisement in the newspaper and, without telling his wife, he bought a small crockery (陶器) factory. The next week he told his family. They were horrified and worried. They thought he was too old at 71 to start work again.\nHe is now 76 and he has expanded the company considerably. He has increased the number of staff from 6 to 24 and he has found many new customers for the products. He has developed the export market and has improved profits by 200%. He has opened a new design office and enpolyed three young designers. They have been all over the world to ger new ideas, and one of them has gone to France this week to a major trade fair. Most importantly, he hasn't been bored since he brought the factory.",questions:[{question:"The topic sentence of Para.1 is_________.",options:["AMorgan Rees has always been a good businessman   ","He used to own three petrol stations asn was busy most of the time","When Morgen Rees was 65, he got retired","Reluctantly, he handed over the business to his son"],answer:"A"},{question:"The topic sentence of Para.2 is_________.     ",options:["he didn't what to do with himself    ","he went on holiday to interesting places with his wife ","he was unhappy after he got retired     ","None of them "],answer:"C"},{question:"Which of the following statements can best express the main idea of Para.3?  ",options:["One day he saw an advertisement in the newspaper","He bought a small crockery factory in seceret and started work again. ","He told his family he bought a small factory.","His family was horried and worried when they learned he bought the small factory."],answer:"B"},{question:"What is the central idea of the last paragraph?    ",options:["Morgan Rees has worked until he is 71.","Morgan Rees has developed the export market and improvedthe profits by 200%","Morgan Rees hasn't been bored since he bought the factory.","Since he started working again, Morgan Rees has expanded the company considerably, which has enriched his retire life.  自从重新开始工作,摩根.里斯显著的扩大了公司的规模,这丰富了他的退休生活."],answer:"D"},{question:"The passage mainly deals with_________.   ",options:["why Morgan Rees bought a small crockery factory","how Morgan Rees lived his retired like more happy by turning to work again. ","how Morgan Rees became a good businessman","how Morgan Rees expanded the company considerably."],answer:"B"}]},{text:"\tWhat makes a person a scientist?\tDoes he have ways or tools of learning that are different from those of others? The answer is \"no\". It is not the tools a scientist uses but how he uses these tools that make him a scientist. You will probably agree that knowing how to use a power is important to a carpenter. You will probably agree, too, that knowing how to investigate, how to discover information, is important to everyone. The scientist, however, goes one step further, he must be sure that he has a reasonable answer to his questions and that his answer can be confirmed by other persons. He also works to fit the answer he gets to many questions into a large set of ideas about how the world works.\n\tThe scientist's knowledge must be exact. There is no room for half right or right just half the time. He must be as nearly right as the conditions permit. What works under one set of conditions at one time must work under the same conditions at other times. If the conditions are different, any changes the scientist observes in a demonstration must be explained by the changes in the conditions. This is one reason that investigations are important in science. Albert Einstein, who developed the theory of relativity, arrived at this theory through mathematics. The accuracy of this mathematics was later tested through investigations, Einstein's ideas were shown to be correct. A scientist uses many tools for measurements. Then the measurements are used to make mathematical calculations that may test his investigations.",questions:[{question:"What makes a scientist according to the passage? ",options:["The tools he uses.\t\t\t\t\t","The way he uses his tools. ","His way of learning.\t\t\t\t\t","The various tools he uses."],answer:"B"},{question:'"The scientist, however, goes one step further…". The author says this to show _______.',options:["the importance of information\t\t\t","the importance of thinking","the difference between scientists and ordinary people","the difference between carpenters and people with other jobs"],answer:"C"},{question:"A sound scientific theory should be one that _______.",options:["works not only under one set of conditions at one time, but also under the same conditions at other times ","does not allow any changes even under different conditions","can be used for many purposes","leave no room for improvement"],answer:"A"},{question:"The author quotes the case of Albert Einstein to illustrate _______.",options:["that measurements are importance to success in science","that accuracy of mathematics","that the investigations are important in science","that the mathematical calculations may test his investigations"],answer:"C"},{question:"What is the main idea of the passage? ",options:["The theory of relativity.\t\t\t\t\t","Exactness is the core of science.","Scientists are different from ordinary people.","Exactness and ways of using tools are the importance to the making of a scientist."],answer:"D"}]},{text:'One day a bookseller (书商) let a big box of books fall on his foot. "Go to see the doctor," said his wife. "No", he said, "I\'ll wait until the doctor comes into the shop next time. Then I\'ll ask him about my foot. If you I go to see him, I\'ll have to pay him."\nOn the next day the doctor came into the shop for some books. When the bookseller was gettinghim ready, he told the doctor about his bagd foot. The doctor look at it. \n"You must put that foot in hot water every night. Then you must put somthing on it," said the deoctor.\nHe took out a piece of paper and wrote on it. "Buy this and put it on the foot before you go to bed every night,"he said.\n" Thank you," said the bookseller. "And now, sir, here are your books."\n"How much?"said the doctor.\n"Two pounds."\n"Good,"said the doctor. "I shall not have to pay you nothing."\n"Why?"asked the bookseller.\n"I told you about your foot. I want two pounds for that. If people come to my house, I ask them to pay one pound for a small thing like that. But when I go to their houses, I want two pounds. And i came here, didn\'t I?"',questions:[{question:"What happened to the bookseller one day ? ",options:["He lost a box of books.              ","His foot was wounded by a box of books.","He lent the doctor a box of books.     ","He sold out all his books. "],answer:"B"},{question:"The bookseller's  wife asked him _________.  ",options:["to go out fo some medecine     ","To send somebody for a doctor","to go to see the doctor     ","To wait for the doctor to come"],answer:"C"},{question:"The bookseller didn't take his wife's advice because _________. ",options:["He was afraid of the doctor      ","He didn't take to take medicine","He couldn't walk by himself     ","He didn't want to pay the doctor  "],answer:"D"},{question:"The doctor paid __________for the books.   ",options:["one pound      ","two pounds      ","Nothing       ","Something"],answer:"C"},{question:"The bookseller paid            moeny for seeing the doctor in the end.",options:["more      ","Less       ","The same amount of       ","no"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Today Newton is a very clean place. Many years ago, however, there were millions of rats in it. They attacked the cats and dogs. Sometimes a great number of them knocked down a man or woman walking home at night. The rats were very large in size and they harmed many people.\nThey goverment ordered everybody to kill rats. Most people were lazy, so they didn't kill many. The goverment promised to pay some money for each dead rat. The made the people very happy. They killed thousands of rats everyday. A goverment officer put all the dead rats in a big pile. Sometimes a man brought hundreds in one day.\nAfter two weeks there were not many rats in the city, but people still brought many rats to the goverment office. The goverment officer thought that people were stealing dad rats from the pile. He ordered his mean to dig a deep hole and put the rats in it. Soon there were no mroe rats, and the goverment didn't pay any more momey.",questions:[{question:"Newton is a place which __________. ",options:["used to be very clean     ","Is no longer a city    ","is very clean   ","Will be very clean"],answer:"C"},{question:"when the goverment first ordered the people to kill rats, the people__________.",options:["Asked for some money for each dead rat       ","Stole dead rats from the pile","Were too lazy to kill many rats    ","Killed nearly all the rats quickly"],answer:"C"},{question:"The people killed rats__________.  ",options:["To get money from the goverment  ","To help the goverment make the city clean","Tomake the goverment officer happy","To protect(保护)their cats and dogs"],answer:"A"},{question:"A deep hole was dug so that ___________.  ",options:["the rats couldn't come out to attack people at night.","people could take rats from it easily","people would kill more rats","nobody could take any rats from the pile "],answer:"D"},{question:"What is the best topic for this passage ? ",options:["How to Kill Rats      ","Newton--- A City of Rats","How Newton Became a Very Clean Place ","How Newton Became a Famous City"],answer:"C"}]},{text:'Mr. Froster lived by himself a long way form town. He hardly ever left his home, but one day he went iinto town to buy some things in the market. After he had bought them, he went into a restaurant ans sat down at a table by himself. When he looked around, he saw several old people put glasses on before reading their  man newspapers, so after lunch he decided to go to a shop to buy himself some glasses too. He walked along the road, and soon found a shop.\nThe man in the shop made him try on a lot of glasses, but Tom always said, "No, i can\'t read with these."\nThe man became more and more puzzled (迷惑不解),until fianlly he said, "Excuse me, but can you read at all?"\n"No, of course i can\'t!" Tom said angrily. "If I was already able to read, do you think i would have come here to buy glasses?"',questions:[{question:"Mr. Forester lived____________.     ",options:["With his family in a city         ","With his family in the countryside","Alone in a city                ","Alone in the countryside   "],answer:"D"},{question:"Tom__________went into town. ",options:["often        ","always      ","Almost never     ","Everyday"],answer:"C"},{question:"The old people in the restaurant read their newspapers__________. ",options:["with glasses on            ","with glasses off  ","With glasses of beer in front of them        ","with glasses pipes in their mouths"],answer:"A"},{question:"The shop Tom went into sold__________.     ",options:["drinking glasses and cups     ","glass for windowss and colors","glasses for people who could not read   ","Glasses for people who could not see well "],answer:"D"},{question:"what kind of mistake did Tom make?  ",options:["He went to the wrong kind of shop.    ","He didn't try on all the glasses in the shop","He thought that a person who had not learned to read would be able to do so if he wore glasses.","He left his money in the restaurant "],answer:"C"}]},{text:'Once James Thornhill, a famous English painter, was asked to paint some pictures on the walls of the king\'s palace in England.\nThen workers were sent for and a big platform(台子) was made.\nWith the help of a worker, Thornhill started painting on the plastform. They worked for a whole yeara and at last the pictures were ready.\nThornhill was happy when he looked at the pictures, for they were really beautifu. He looked at them for a long time, and then took one step back and looked again. Now the pictures were even more beautiful. He took another step, then another. Finally he was at the very edge of the platform, but he didn\'t know it because he was thinking of his picture. \nThe worker saw everything. "what should i do?" he thought. "Thornhill was at the very edge of the platform. If I cry out, he will take another step, fall off in and surely be killed." So the worker quickly took some paint (漆)and threw iin at the pictures.\n"what are you doing?"cried the painter, running quickly forward to his pictures.\n',questions:[{question:"James Thornhill was an English____________. ",options:["worker       ","artist       ","King       ","writer "],answer:"B"},{question:"He was ordered to__________.     ",options:["paint the wall of king's palace in England. ","paint some pictures on the wall of the palace. ","build a big platform in front of the palace","put up some new pictures on the old wall."],answer:"B"},{question:"It took them ___________ to finish the pictures.  ",options:["a month      ","a week     ","tewelve months       ","Half a month"],answer:"C"},{question:"James Thornhill felt that the________he was from the pictures, the _______they were.",options:["nearer... more beautiful              ","father... more ugly ","father... more beautiful     ","Higher above... more good-looking "],answer:"C"},{question:"The worker threw some paint at the pictures in order no         .  ",options:["save Jame's life     ","destory the picture","make the picture more beautiful           ","make the king angrey"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'The United States covers a large part of the North American continent. Its neighbors are Canada to the north and Mexico to the south. Although the United States is a big country , it is not the largest in the world. In 2000, its population was over 222 million.\nWhen this land first became a nation, after winning its independence from England, it had thirteen states. Each of the states was represented on the American flag by a star. All these were in the eastern part of the continent. As the nation grew toward the west, new states were added and new stars appeared on the flag. For a long time, there were 48 stars. In 1959, however, two more stars were added to the flag, representing the new states of Alaska and Hawaii. \nIndians were the first people of the land which is now the United States. There are still many thousands of Indians now living in all parts of the country. Sometimes it is said that the Indians are "the only real Americans". Most Americans come from all over the world. Those who came first in greatest numbers to make their homes on the eastern of North America were mostly from England. It is for the reason that the language of the United States is English and that its culture and customs are more like those of England than those of any other country in the world.',questions:[{question:"Which of the following is TURE?  ",options:["American is the largest country in the world.","The United States lies next to Canada and Mexico. 美国邻近加拿大和墨西哥.","America covers most part of the North American continent.","Mexico is to the north of Canada."],answer:"B"},{question:"After winning its independence, the United States              . ",options:["had nothing to do with England         ","made India part of its land ","mianly developed westward            ","took over parts of Canada and Mexico"],answer:"C"},{question:"The United States didn't have__________states until__________. ",options:["thirteen;1959     ","fifty;1959     ","fifty;this land first became a nation      ","fifty;1964"],answer:"B"},{question:"Why is English the language of America?  ",options:["Because English is the native language of the Indians. ","Because most Americans come from all over the world. ","Because Canada is America's nearest neighbor. ","Because most of the people who first settled in America were from England."],answer:"D"},{question:'The best title for the passage is "____________".  ',options:["the States of America            ","The language of America","The United States of America      ","The Culture and Customs of America"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"The residents of 24 Acacia Grove were dissatisfied with the condition of the property, so John Preston called a meeting to discuss things last week. At the meeting John suggested setting up a residents' committee. Everyone was so worried and angry about the agent's inactivity that they agreed, and they elected John as chairman of the committee. Many residents said that they were tired of telephoning the agent and tired of complaining about the flats. Although the agent was responsible for the flats, they thought that he didn't do enough. Therefore John was asked to write to the agent and say that they were disappointed with the management of the flats. \nThe next service payment was due at the end of the month. However, they agreed not to pay it until they were happy with the plans to improve the property. They decided to tell the agent that he must start the work within one month. They all went away very pleased with themselves.",questions:[{question:"Why did John Preston call a meeting last week?   ",options:["Because the residents were dissatisfied with the presents' committee.","Because the residents were dissatisfied with the bad management of the flats.  ","Because some residents requested to change the present residents' committee.","Because he wanted to become chairman of the committee."],answer:"B"},{question:"Who elected John as chairman of the committee?   ",options:["The agent     ","the residents       ","the committee      ","Acacia Grove "],answer:"B"},{question:'What does the word "inactivity" mean in the thrid sentence in Para.1? ',options:["weakness       ","Progress       ","State        ","Lace of actions  "],answer:"D"},{question:'What does the word "due" mean in the first sentence in Para.2? ',options:["to be paid        ","Proper         ","Owed         ","large "],answer:"A"},{question:"When did they agree to pay the next service payment ? ",options:["at the end of the month         ","Within one month      ","When they were happy with the plans to improve the property. ","The agent would tell them."],answer:"C"}]},{text:"When I was a little girl, my brothers and i collected stamps for many years. My mother didn't use to work during the week, but she worked in the post office near our house on Saturdays and she used to bring home all the new stamps as soon as they were issued(发行).\nOn the day of World Cup football final in London in 1996, we were very excited because England were playing West Germany in the final. When we were having lunch, my mother told us to go to the post office straight way after the match if England won,  but she didn't tell us why. At 2 O'clock my mother went back to work as usual, while the rest of the family were watching the football on TV at home. Although she wasn't watching the match, she was listening to it on the readio.\nEngland won 4:2 and so my brothers and I ran to the post office. As we burst in, my mother was standing behind the counter. She was waiting to sell us a very special limited edition with ENGLAND WINNDERS on eah stamp. We were over the moon.\nWe still have it today, and perhaps it is worth a lot of money.\n",questions:[{question:"This passage mainly tell us           .    ",options:["The auther and her brother used to like stamps very muhch","The auther had a very kind mother","The auther and her brother had an unforgetable experience in collecting stamps ","their mother used to support them by working in the post office."],answer:"C"},{question:"Accordin to the passage, her mother worked in the post office           .",options:["During the week     ","on Saturdays       ","On Sundays     ","For six days "],answer:"B"},{question:"Their mother told them to go to the post office straight away after the match if England won, but she didn't tell them why.  Why do you think she did that ?  母亲告诉他们比赛结束后如果英格兰队获胜了就直接去邮局但是她没告诉他们为什么. 你认为母亲为什么那样做?",options:["She wanted to give them a surprise. ","She doubted if she would get the stamps ","She forgot to do that.             ","She thought is unneccessary to tell them the reason."],answer:"A"},{question:'What does the sentence "We were over the moon" mean ?  ',options:["we jumped high    ","We were extremly happy about it. ","We watched the moon of a long time      ","We couldn't sleep the whole night"],answer:"B"},{question:"What is the best title for this passage ? ",options:["My childhood      ","My mother   ","A precious Stamp    ","A memorable Experience in Collecting Stamps    "],answer:"D"}]},{text:"When John and Victoria Falls arrived in New York City for one-year stay, they did not bring very many things with them. They had planned either to live in a furnished apartment or to buy used furniture. But they soon learned about a new system that more and more people are using. The renting of home furnishings (bed, tables, dishes, and so on) has become one of America's fastest growing businesses.\nWhat kinds of people rent their home furnishings instead of buying them? People who are international business or government officials, foreign students, airline workers, young married couple - people whose job or business may force them to move frequently from one city to another. They save a lot of trouble and the cost of moving their furniture each time. They simply rent new furniture when they reach their new homes. Young people with little money do not want to buy cheap furniture that they may soon dislike. They prefer to wait until they have enough money to buy furniture that they really like. Meanwhile, they find they can rent better quality furniture than they could afford to buy.\nOne family, who now have a large, beautiful home of their own, liked their rented furniture so much that they decided to keep renting it instead of buying new things. But usually people don't like to tell others about it. The idea of renting home furnishings is still quite new, and they are not sure what their neighbors might think. (248words)",questions:[{question:"Which of the following has become one of America's fastest growing businesses? ____________",options:["Selling home furnishings.","Renting furnished apartments.","Selling used furniture.","Renting home furnishings. "],answer:"D"},{question:"Why do some people prefer to rent furniture? ____________",options:["Because the furniture they get in this way is new.","Because it saves them a lot of money.","Because it saves them much trouble and money. ","Because they can always get better quality furniture in this way."],answer:"C"},{question:"What can you infer from the passage? ____________         ",options:["The idea of renting furniture is not acceptable.","Renting furniture is not popular in the couple's home town. ","Only those who don't have enough money to rent furniture.","People usually grow to like the furniture they have rented."],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following can best serve as the title of the passage? ____________",options:["Rent or Buy?\t\t","A New Way of Getting Home Furnishings.  ","Furnished Apartments.\t","A New Idea."],answer:"B"},{question:"Young people liked renting home furniture in that __________.",options:["They have less money","They don't want to buy old furniture","The new furniture is of good quality","They don't have much money and don't want to buy the cheap furniture"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"\tA characteristic of American culture that has become almost a tradition is to respect the self-made man - the man who has risen to the top through his own efforts, usually beginning by working with his hands. While the leader in business or industry or the college professor occupies a higher social position and commands greater respect in the community than the common laborer or even the skilled factory worker, he may take pains to point out that his father started life in America as a farmer or laborer of some sort.\n\tThis attitude toward manual(体力的)labor is now still seen many aspects of American life. One is invited to dinner at a home that is not only comfortably but even luxuriously(豪华地)furnished and in which there is every evidence of the fact the family has been able to afford foreign travel, expensive hobbies, and college education for the children; yet the hostess probably will cook the dinner herself, will serve it herself and will wash dishes afterward, furthermore the dinner will not consist merely of something quickly and easily assembled from contents of various cans and a cake or a pie bought at the nearby bakery. On the contrary, the hostess usually takes pride in careful preparation of special dishes. A professional may talk about washing the car, digging in his flowerbeds, painting the house. His wife may even help with these things, just as he often helps her with the dishwashing. The son who is away at college may wait on table and wash dishes for his living, or during the summer he may work with a construction gang on a highway in order to pay for his education.",questions:[{question:"From paragraph 1, we know that in America _______.",options:["people tend to have a high opinion of the self-made man ","people can always rise to the top through their own efforts","college professors win great respect from common workers","people feel painful to mention their fathers as labors"],answer:"A"},{question:"According to the passage, the hostess cooks dinner herself mainly because _______.",options:["servants in American are hard to get\t\t","she takes pride in what she can do herself ","she can hardly afford servants\t\t\t","It is easy to prepare a meal with canned food"],answer:"B"},{question:'The expression "wait on table" in the second paragraph means "_______".',options:["work in a furniture shop\t\t\t\t\t","keep accounts for a bar","wait to lay the table\t\t\t\t\t","serve customers in a restaurant "],answer:"D"},{question:"The author's attitude towards manual(体力的)labor is _______.",options:["positive\t\t","negative\t\t\t","humorous\t\t\t","critical"],answer:"A"},{question:"Which of the following may serve as the best title of the passage? ",options:["A Respectable Self-made Family.\t\t\t","American Attitude toward Manual Labor. ","Characteristics of American Culture.\t\t","The Development of Manual Labor."],answer:"B"}]},{text:"How men first learnt to invent words is unknown; in other words, the origin of language is a mystery. All we really know is that men, unlike animals, somehow invented certain sounds to express thought and feelings, actions and things, so that they could communicate with each other; and that later they agreed upon certain signs, called letters, which could be combined to present those sounds, and which could be written down. Those sounds, whether spoken or written in letters, we call words.\n\tThe power of words, then, lies in their associations-the thing they bring up before our minds. Words become filled with meaning for us by experience; and the longer we live, the more certain words recall to us the glad and sad events of our past; and the more we read and learn, the more the number of words that mean something increases.\n\tGreat writers are those who not only have great thoughts but also express these thoughts in words which appeal powerfully to our minds and emotions. This charming and telling use of words is what we call literary style. Above all, the real poet is a master of words. He can convey his meaning in words which sing like music and which by their position and association can move men to tears. We should therefore learn to choose our words carefully and use them accurately, or they will make our speech silly and vulgar.",questions:[{question:"The origin of language is _______.  ",options:["a legend handed down from the past\t\t","a matter that is hidden or secret","a question difficult to answer\t\t\t\t","a problem not yet solved "],answer:"D"},{question:"What is true about words?      ",options:["They are used to express feelings only.\t\t","They can not be written down.","They are simply sounds.\t\t","They are mysterious."],answer:"C"},{question:"The real power of words lies in their _______.  ",options:["properties\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","characteristics\t\t","peculiarity\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","representative function    "],answer:"D"},{question:'By "association", the author means _______.  ',options:["a special quality\t\t\t\t\t\t","a joining of ideas in the mind ","an appearance which is puzzling\t\t\t","a strange feature"],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following statements about the real poet is NOT true?",options:["He is no more than a master of words.\t\t","He can convey his ideas in words which sing like music.","He can move men to tears.\t\t\t\t","His style is always charming."],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Shyness is the cause of much unhappiness for a great many people. Shy people are anxious and self-conscious; that is, they are excessively concerned with their own appearance and actions. Worrisome thoughts are constantly occurring in their minds: what kind of impression am I making? Do they like me? Do I sound stupid? Am I wearing unattractive clothes?\n\tIt is obvious that such uncomfortable feelings must negatively affect people. A person's conception of himself or herself is reflected in the way he or she behaves, and the way a person behaves affects other people's reactions. In general, the way people think about themselves has a profound effect on all areas of their lives.\n\tShy people, having low self-esteem, are likely to be passive and easily influenced by others. They need reassurance that they are doing \"the right thing.\" Shy people are very sensitive to criticism; they feel it confirms their feelings of inferiority. They also find it difficult to be pleased by compliment with a statement like this one, \"You're just saying that to make me feel good. I know it's not true.\" It is clear that while self-awareness is a healthy quality, overdoing it is harmful.\n\tCan shyness be completely eliminated, or at least reduced? Fortunately, people can overcome shyness with determined and patient efforts in building self-confidence. Since shyness goes hand in hand with a lack of self-esteems, it is important for people to accept their weakness as well as their strengths.\n\tEach one of us is a unique, worthwhile individual, interested in our own personal ways. The better we understand ourselves, the easier it becomes to live up to our full potential. Let's not allow shyness to block our chances for a rich and fulfilling life.",questions:[{question:'What does the author try to prove by citing "what kind of impression am I making?"',options:["Shy people benefit from their caring about their appearance.","People's shyness made them care too much about their appearance and actions.","It's natural that shy people don't believe other's compliments.","Shy people think they are different from others."],answer:"B"},{question:"According to the writer, self-awareness is _______.",options:["a good quality\t\t\t\t\t\t","the cause of unhappiness","harmful to people\t\t\t\t\t\t","a weak point of shy people"],answer:"A"},{question:"When being praised, shy people feel that it is _______.",options:["good\t\t\t\t","unreal\t ","very reasonable\t\t","harmful"],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following statements is true according to the passage? ",options:["Shyness helps us to develop our potential.\t","Shyness enables us to understand ourselves better.","Shyness can block our chances for a rich life. ","Shyness has nothing to do with lack of self-esteem."],answer:"C"},{question:"It can be inferred from the passage that shy people _______.",options:["should find more of their weakness\t\t","should understand themselves in the right way ","had better ignore their weakness\t\t\t","can get rid of their shyness while maintaining low self-esteem"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"In the United States, it is not customary to telephone someone very early in the morning. If you telephone him early in the day, while he is shaving or having breakfast, the time of the call shows that the matter is very important and requires immediate attention. The same meaning is attached to telephone calls made after 11:00 p.m. If someone receives a call during sleeping hours, he assumes it's a matter of life or death. The time chosen for the call communicates its importance. In social life, time plays a very important part. In the U.S.A. guests tend to feel they are not highly regarded if the invitation to a dinner party is extended only three or four days before the party date. But it is not true in all countries. In other areas of the world, it may be considered foolish to make an appointment too far in advance because plans which are made for a date more than a week away tend to be forgotten. The meaning of time differs in different parts of the world. Thus, misunderstandings arise between people from different cultures that treat time differently. Promptness is valued highly in American life, for example. If people are not prompt, they may be regarded as impolite or not fully responsible. In the U.S. no one would think of keeping a business associate waiting for an hour, it would be too impolite. A person who is 5 minutes late, will say a few words of explanation, though perhaps he will not complete the sentence. (260 words)",questions:[{question:"What is the main idea of this passage? __________  ",options:["It is not customary to telephone someone in the morning and in sleeping hours in the U.S.","The role of time in social life over the world. ","If people are not prompt, they may be regarded as impolite or not fully responsible in the U.S.","Not every country treats the concept of time as the same."],answer:"B"},{question:"What does it mean in the passage if you call someone during his or her sleeping hours? __________",options:["A matter of work.","A matter of life or death. ","You want to see him or her.","You want to make an appointment with him or her."],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following time is proper if you want to make an appointment with your friend? __________",options:["at 7: 00 am.\t\t\t","at 4:00 pm.\t\t\t","at the midnight.\t\t","at 4:00 am. "],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following statements is true according to the passage? __________",options:["In the U.S.A guests tend to feel they are highly regarded if the invitation to a dinner party is extended only three or four days before the party date.","There is no misunderstanding arising between people from different cultures about the concept of time.","It may be considered foolish to make an appointment well in advance in the U.S.A..","Promptness is valued highly in American life. "],answer:"D"},{question:"From the passage we can safely infer that __________.  ",options:["it's a matter of life or death if you call someone in day time","the meaning of time differs in different parts of the world  ","it makes no difference in the U.S. whether you are early or late for a business party","if a person is late for a date, he needn't make some explanation"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"There are three kinds of goals: short-term, medium-range and long-term goals.\nShort-term goals are those that usually deal with current activities, which we can apply on a daily basis. Such goals can be achieved in a week or less, or two weeks, or possibly, months. It should be remembered that just as a building is no stronger than its foundation, long-term goals cannot amount to very much without the achievement of solid short-term goals. Upon completing our short-term goals, we should date the occasion and then add new short-term goals that will build on those that have been completed.\nThe intermediate goals build on the foundation of the short-term goals. They might deal with just one term of school or the entire school year, or they could even extend for several years. Any time you move a step at a time, you should never allow yourself to become discouraged or overwhelmed. As you complete each step, you will enforce the belief in your ability to grow and succeed. And as your list of completion dates grow, your motivation and desire will increase.\nLong-term goals may be related to our dreams of the future. They might cover five years or more. Life is not a static thing. We should never allow a long-term goal to limit us or our course of action.(221 words)",questions:[{question:"Our long-term goals mean a lot ____________.",options:["If we cannot reach solid short-term goals\t\t","If we complete the short-term goals","If we have dreams of the future\t\t\t\t","If we put forward some plans"],answer:"B"},{question:"New short-term goals are built upon ____________.  ",options:["a daily basis\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","your achievement in a week","current activities\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","the goals that have been completed"],answer:"D"},{question:"When we complete each step of our goals, ____________.",options:["we will win final success\t\t\t\t\t","we are overwhelmed","we should build up confidence of success\t\t","we should have strong desire for setting new goals"],answer:"C"},{question:"What is the main idea of this passage? ____________.",options:["Life is a dynamic thing.\t\t\t\t\t     ","we should set up long-term goals","Different kinds of goals in life.\t ","The limitation of long-term goals."],answer:"C"},{question:"Which of the following statements is wrong according to the passage? ____________",options:["The long-term goals cannot amount to very much without the achievement of solid short-term goals","The intermediate goals build on the foundation of the short-term goals.","Life is a static thing, thus we should never allow a long-term goal to limit us or our course of action.","We should often add new short-term goals to those which have been completed."],answer:"C"}]},{text:"\tMany people who work in London prefer to live outside it, and to go in to their offices or schools every day by train, car or bus, even though this means they have to get up early in the morning and reach home late in the evening.\n\tOne advantage of living outside London is that houses are cheaper. Even a small flat in London without a garden costs quite a lot to rent. With the same money, one can get a little house in the country with a garden of one's own.\n\tThen, in the country one can really get away from the noise and hurry of busy working lives. Even though one has to get up earlier and spend more time in trains or buses, one can sleep better at night and during weekends and on summer evenings, one can enjoy the fresh, clean air of the country. If one likes gardens, one can spend one's free time digging, planting, watering and doing the hundred and one other jobs which are needed in a garden. Then, when the flowers and vegetables come up, one has got the reward together with those who have shared the secret of Nature.\n\tSome people, however, take no interest in country things: for them, happiness lies in the town, with its cinemas and theatres, beautiful shops and busy streets, dance-halls and restaurants. Such people would feel that their life was not worth living if they had to live it outside London. An occasional walk in one of the parks and a fortnight's (two weeks) visit to the sea every summer is all the country they want: the rest they are quite prepared to leave to those who are glad to get away from London every night.",questions:[{question:"Which of the following statements is NOT true? ",options:["People who love Nature prefer to live outside the city.","All the people who work in London prefer to live in the country. ","Some people enjoying city life prefer to work and live inside London.","Many nature lovers, though working in London, prefer to live outside the city."],answer:"B"},{question:"With the same money needed for _______, one can buy a little house with a garden in the country.",options:["getting a small flat with a garden\t\t\t","having a small flat with a garden","renting a small flat without a garden\t\t","buying a small flat without a garden\t"],answer:"C"},{question:"When the garden is in blossom, the one _______ has been rewarded.",options:["living in the country\t\t","having spent time working in the garden","having a garden of his own\t","having been digging, planting and watering"],answer:"B"},{question:"People who think happiness lies in the city life would feel that _______ if they had to live outside London.",options:["their life was meaningless\t\t","their life was invaluable ","they didn't deserve a happy life\t\t\t\t\t","they were not worthy of their happy life"],answer:"A"},{question:"The underlined phrase get away from in the 3rd paragraph refers to _______.",options:["deal with\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","do away with ","escape from\t\t\t\t","prevent from"],answer:"C"}]}],d=[{text:'A foreigner\'s first impression of the U.S. is likely to be that everyone is in a rush-often under pressure. City people appear always to be hurrying to get where they are going restlessly, seeking attention in a store, and elbowing others as they try to complete their errands (任务). Racing through daytime meals is part of the pace of life in this country.\nWorking time is considered precious. Others in public eating places are waiting for you to finish so that they too can be served and get back to work within the time allowed. Each person hurries to make room for the next person. If you don\'t, waiters will hurry you.\nYou also find drivers will be abrupt and that people will push past you. You will miss smiles, brief conversations, and small courtesies with strangers. Don\'t take it personally. This is because people value time highly, and they resent someone else "wasting" it beyond a certain courtesy point.\n      The view of time affects the importance we attach to patience. In the American system of values, patience is not a high priority. Many of us have what might be called "a short fuse." We begin to move restlessly about if we feel time is slipping away without some returnbe this in terms of pleasure, work value, or rest. Those coming from lands where time is looked upon differently may find this matter of pace to be one of their most difficult adjustments in both business and daily life.\nMany newcomers to the States will miss the opening courtesy of a business call, for example, they will miss the ritual socializing that goes with a welcoming cup of tea or coffee they may be traditional in their own country. They may miss leisurely business chats in a café or coffeehouse. Normally, Americans do not assess their visitors in such relaxed surroundings over prolonged small talks. We seek out evidence of past performance rather than evaluate a business colleague through social courtesies. Since we generally assess and probe professionally rather than socially, we start talking business very quickly. (348 words)\n',questions:[{question:"The statement that Americans are impolite to their business colleagues is wrong.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'In the fourth paragraph, "a high priority" means a "first concern". ',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Americans evaluate a business colleague by establishing business relations.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"This passage mainly talks about now Americans do business with foreigners.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"We can infer from the passage that the author's tone is writing is praiseful.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'There was once an ant that was very thirsty.\n    It ran here and there looking for some water but could not find any.\n    Then suddenly, when the ant was almost ready to die of thirst, a large drop of water fell on it.\n    The ant drank the water, which saved its life.\n    The water was actually a tear from a young girl who was crying. Because of her sadness, the tear had magical qualities and suddenly the ant could speak the language of human beings.\n    The ant looked up and saw the young girl sitting in front of a huge pile of seeds.\n    "Why are you sad?" asked the ant.\n    "I\'m the prisoner of a giant." the girl told the ant. "He won\'t let me go until I\'ve made three separate heaps of grain, barley(大麦)and rye(黑麦)out of this huge pile of seeds in which they are all mixed together."\n    "That will take you a month!" the ant said, looking at the huge pile of seeds.\n    "I know," the girl cried, "and if I haven\'t finished by tomorrow, the giant will eat me for his supper!"\n    "Don\'t cry," the ant said, "my friends and I will help you."\n    Soon thousands of ants were at work, separating the three kinds of seeds.\n    The next morning, when the giant saw that the work had been done, he let the girl go. \n    Thus it was one of her tears that saved her life. ',questions:[{question:"The ant was playing when it ran here and there.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The drop of water fell on the ant when it was nearly dying.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The young girl was crying because she wanted to have supper.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The giant would eat the girl if she failed to do the work.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The ant's friends saved the girl's life. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"In choosing a friend, one should be very careful. A good friend can help you study. You can have fun together and make each other happy. Sometimes you will meet fair weather friends. They will be with you as long as you have money or luck, but when you are down, they will run away. How do i know when i found a good friend? I look for certain qualities of character, especially understanding, honesty and reliability(可靠).\nA good friend, above all else, tries to understand how another person is feeling. He is not quick to judge. Instead , he tries to learn from others. He puts himself in the other person's place, and the tries to think of ways to be helpful. He is also a good listener. \nAt the same time, a good friend is honest. He does not look for faults in others. He notices their good points. In short, a friend will try to understand me and accept me. \nAnother quality of a friend is reliability. I can always depend on a good friend. If he tells me he will meet me somewhere at a certain time. I can be sure that he will be there. If i need a favor, he will also do his best to help me. If i am in trouble, he will not run away from me. \nWhen i meet someone who is reliable, honest, and understanding. I know I've found a friend. ",questions:[{question:"The writer thinks that one of the important qualities in choosing a friend is understanding. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"If you have fair weather friends, you will be lucky. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Good friends need to understand each other's feelings. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"This passage is mainly discussing the qualities of a friend.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The meaning of the phrase "a fair weather friend" underlined in the 1st paragraph is a friend who shares difficulties with you. ',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"No one is glad to hear that his body has to be cut open by a surgeon and part of it taken out. Today, however, we needn't worry about feeling pain during the operation. The sick person falls into a kind of sleep, and when he awakes, the operation is finished. But these happy conditions are fairly new. It is not many years since a man who had to have operation felt all in its pain.\nLong ago, operation has usually to be done while the sick man could feel everything. Sooner after 1770, Joseph Priestley discovered a gas which is now called \"laughing gas\". Laughing as became known in America. Young men and women went to parties to try it. Most of them spent their time laughing, but one man at a party, Horace Wells, noticed that people didn't seem to feel pain when they were using this gas. He decided to make an experiment on himself. He asked a friend to help him.\nWells took some of the gas, and his friend pulled out one of Well's teeth. Wells felt no pain at all. \nAs he didn't know enough about laughing gas, he gave a man less gas than he should have. The man cried out with pain when his tooth was being pulled out.\nWells tried again, but this time he gave too much of the gas, and the man died. Wells never forgot this terrible event. \n",questions:[{question:"It is no long since a man felt all the pain while being operated. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Long ago, when the sick man was operated on, he could feel nothing. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Using the laughing gas, the people seemed to feel pain during the operation. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"If a man took less laughing gas than he should have when an operation went on, he still felt pain. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"One who took too much of the laughing gas would die. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Mr. White lived in a small village. His parents hadn\'t enough money to send him to school. He had to help them to do something in the fields. But he didn\'t like to live in the poor place. When he was sixteen, he got to the town and found work in a factory. Three years later he became tall and strong. So he was sent to Africa as a soldier. He stayed there for five years and got some money. Then he came back to England and bought a shop in a small town. No people in the town went to Africa except him. And he hoped they thought he was a famous man and that they could respect him. The children often asked him to tell them some stories and his life in Africa.\nOne day a few children asked him to tell them something about the animals in Africa. He told them how he fought with the tigers and elephants. His stories surprised them all and some policemen and workers went to listen to him. It made him happier. Just a man who taught geography in a middle school passed there. He stopped to listen to him for a while and then said, "Could you please tell us a rare animal, sir?"\n"Certainly," said Mr. Turner. "One day I met a rhinoceros(犀牛) by a river..."\n"Please wait a minute, sir," said the man. "There aren\'t any rhinoceros in Africa at all!"\n "It\'s rare just because there aren\'t any!" ',questions:[{question:"Mr. White was born in a farmer's family. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Mr. White hoped to be respected because he was the richest man in their town. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The children often asked him to tell them something interesting because he knew more than any other person in the town. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"All people believed Mr. White except the children.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Mr. White wouldn't like to admit that he was wrong",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"If you travel by air across the center of Africa or South America, you fly over forests for thousands of kilometers. These great forests are the oceans of trees. There are thousands and thousands of different kinds of plants and animals.\n    However, the world's forests are getting smaller all the time. We are cutting down the trees because we need wood, and we need more farmland. Some people say that there will not be any forests like these in 20 or 30 years. What will happen if they disappear?\nIf we cut down our forests, a lot of plants and animals will disappear from the world. In a lot of places the new farmland will soon look like the old deserts. Crops will not grow there. It will not rain very often, and the weather will get very hot. Perhaps the climate of the world will change. This will be dangerous for everyone in the world. That is why we must take care of our forests. ",questions:[{question:"The passage mainly tells us about the importance of taking care of plants. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Forests are homes for different kinds of animals. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The need for more wood and more land help to protect our forests. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"We'll have more and greater forestsn in 20 or 30 years in some people's view. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The writer thinks it necessary to protect the forests. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Martin Luther King was a black minister, who became a great leader of the civil rights movement in the 1950s and 1960s.\nKing was born on January 15, 1929 in Atlanta, Georgia. When he was young, he was strongly influenced by Thoreau and Indian leader Mahatma Gandhi\'s idea of non-violent resistance. Having received a Ph. D (Doctor of Philosophy) from Boston University, he became a political and religious leader of the non-violent civil relights movement in 1955. On August 28, 1963, he led over 250,000 Americans on a march in Washington D.C. to fight for the Civil Rights Law to guarantee equality for all people, and delivered his best known speech "I Have a Dream" before the Lincoln Memorial. The "dream" is a dream of brotherly love and equality for the Black and White. Thus, he was awarded the Nobel Prize for peace in 1964, but he was murdered four years later.\nThough he died, he was greatly respected and loved by the Americans, both the white and the black. By vote of Congress in 1968, the third Monday of every January is now a federal holiday in Luther King\'s honor. He lives in people\'s hearts forever. ',questions:[{question:"Martin Luther King was murdered when he was 39 years old.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Martin Luther King was a black minister only.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Martin Luther King's Day has been a federal holiday for more than 40 years.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The underlined word "delivered" in the second paragraph could be replaced by "gave".',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The best title for this passage is "Civil Rights Law".',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"The French Revolution broke out in 1789. At the time France was in a crisis. The government was badly run and people's lives were miserable. King Louis XIV tried to control the national parliament and raise more taxes. But his effort failed. He ordered his troops to Versailles. The people thought that Louis intended to put down the Revolution by force. On July 14,1789, they stormed and took the Bastille, where political prisoners were kept. Ever since that day, July 14 has been the French National Day. Louis tried to flee the country in 1792 to get support from Austria and Prussia. However, he was caught and put in prison. In September 1792, the monarchy was abolished. In the same year, Louis was executed. A few months later his wife, Marie also had her head cut off. The Revolution of France had frightened the other kings of Europe. Armies from Austria and Prussia began to march against France. The French raised republican armies to defend the nation. The Revolution went through a period of terror. Thousands of people lost their lives. In the end, power passed to Napoleon Bonaparte. (190 words)",questions:[{question:"The passage is about the French Revolution? ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The national economy was developing rapidly in 1789. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The political prisoners kept in Prussia? ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The underlined word "abolished" means "ended". ',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The effect of the Revolution was that the King tried to control the national parliament.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'There was once many sheiks (阿拉伯的酋长)who wanted to marry Queen Maura, for she was one of the most beautiful queens of Arabia. \nHowever, she did not like most of the sheiks, and soon there were only three left on her list of possible husbands. \nThese three sheiks were all equally young and handsome, rich and strong.\nIt was very hard for the Queen to choose the best one. \nOne evening, she disguised herself and went to where the three sheiks were having there evening meal.\nShe asked them to give her something to eat.\nThe first sheik gave her some stale(不新鲜的)food left over from the day before.\nThe second sheik gave her a tough piece of old camel\'s tail. \nThe third sheik, whose name was Hakim, gave her some of the most tender (嫩的)and tasty meat. \nAfter the mean, Queen Maura left the sheik\'s camp.\nThe next day, she invited the three sheiks to dinner at her palace. \nShe told her servants to give each sheik what he had given her the evening before. \nHakim, who received a plate of tender and tasty mean, would not eat in unless the other two sheiks could share it with him.\nQueen Maura was now certain which of the sheiks she wanted to marry. \n"Hakim is the most generous of you," she told them, "so i want to marry him ans he will become king."',questions:[{question:"The queen was looking for a husband. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The Queen disguised herself because she didn't want to be recognized by the sheiks.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"She gave the sheiks some stale food to eat the next evening.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Hakim wanted to eat his meal because it was very tasty.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The Queen finally decided to marry Hakim the next evening after the meal. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Sixteen-year-old Maria was waiting in line at the airport in Santo Domingo. She was leaving her native country to join her sister in the United States. She spoke English very well. Though she was very happy she could go abroad, she was feeling sad at leaving her family and fiends. As she was thinking all about this, she suddenly heard the airline employee asking her to pick up her luggage and put it on the scales(称). Maria pulled and pulled. The bag was too heavy and she just couldn\'t lift it up. The man behind her got very impatient. He, too, was waiting to check in his luggage.\n "What\'s wrong with this girl?" He said, "Why doesn\'t she hurry up?" He moved forward and placed his bag on the counter, hoping to check in fist. He was in a hurry to get a good seat.\nMaria was very angry, but she was very polite. And in her best English she said, "Why are you so upset? There are enough seats for everyone on the plane. If you are in such a hurry, why can\'t you give me a hand with my luggage?"\nThe man was surprised to hear Maria speak English. He quickly picked up her luggage and stepped back. Everyone was looking at him with disapproval. (224 words)',questions:[{question:"Maria's story happened B. on her way back to Santo. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"You believe that the work of the airline employee mentioned in the story is to check people's luggage the airport.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'"Why are you so upset?" Maria said to the man. She wanted to tell him that he should not be unhappy and worried.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'"Everyone was looking at him with disapproval." This sentence means that the people around felt sorry for Maria\'s manners.  ',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The author mentioned Maria's age at the beginning of the story in order to show that she was young but behaved properly. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'There was once a man in South America who had a parrot (鹦鹉), a pet bird that could imitate (模拟)human speech. The parrot was unique. There was no other bird like him in the while world. He could lean to say any word except one. He could not say the name of his native town, Cotano. The man did everything he could to teach the parrot to say "Cotano" but he never succeeded. At first he was very gentle with the bird, but gradually he lost his temper. "You stupid bird! Why can\'t you learn to say that one word! Say Cotano or I\'ll like you!"  But the parrot would not say it. Many times the man screamed (大声叫),"Say Cotano or I\'ll kill you!" But the bird would never repeat the name. Finally the man gave up. He picked up the parrot and threw him into the chicken house. "You are even more stupid than the chickens!"\nIn the chicken house, there were four old chickens waiting to be killed for Sunday\'s dinner. The next morning, when he went out to the chicken house, the man opened the door. He was shocked by what he saw. He could not believe his eyes and ears. On the floor lay three dead chickens, the parrot was screaming at the fourth, "Say Catano or I\'ll kill you!".',questions:[{question:"The reason why the parrot couldn't say the name of his native town is not mentioned in the story. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The man lost his temper at the fact that the bird failed to say the name of the town. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The man in the kitchen killed the three chickens. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The bird managed to escape from the chicken house.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The man loved his parrot very much and always treated it kindly. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Started in 1636, Harvard University is the oldest of all the many colleges and universities in the United States. Yale, Princeton, Columbia and Dartmouth were opened soon after Harvard.\nIn the early years, these schools were much alike. Only young men went to college. All the students studied the same subjects, and everyone learned Latin, Greek and Hebrew. Little was known about science then, and one kind of school could teach everything that was known about the world. When the students graduated, most of them become ministers or teachers.\nIn 1782, Harvard stared a medical school for young men who wanted to become doctors. Later lawyers could receive their training in Harvard's low school. In 1825, besides Latin and Greek, Havard began teaching modern languages, such as French and German. Soon it began teaching American history. \nAs knowledge increased, Havard and other colleges began to teach many new subjects. Students were allowed to choose the subjects that interests them.\nToday, there are many different kinds of colleges and universities. Most of them are made up of smaller schools that deal with special fields of learning. There's so much to learn that one kind of school can't offer it all. ",questions:[{question:"The oldest university in the US is Havard. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"From the second paragraph, we can see that in the early years, those colleges and universities were the same. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Modern languages the Harvard taught in 1825 were French and German. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"As knowledge increased, colleges began to teach everything that was known.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"On the whole, the passage is about how colleges have changed. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"The undersea world is very beautiful. Now more and more people want to dive in the water to find the secrets there. Scuba(戴水肺) diving is a new sport today. It can take you into a wonderful undersea world.\nYou will find many strange animals in the sea. Some are like a school bus. Many sea animals give out light in the dark and some have sharp teeth.\nDuring the day, there is enough light. Here, under the sea, everything is blue and green. When fish swim nearby, you can catch them, with your hands. When you have bottles of air on your back, you can stay in deep water for a long time. However, you can't dive too deep. And you must be very careful when you dive in deep water. \nThe deep sea is not an easy place to live in. It is cold, and it is dark, too. The deeper it is, the less sunlight there is. About 3000 feet, there is no light at all. It is very dark in the sea. Many fishes have no eyes. Some have big eyes. A few have eyes on one side. \nBesides, the coldness and the darkness, deep-sea animals face a third danger-other animals.\nAnimals eat! They must find food to eat. Many animals eat plants. However, some animals eat meat. This means these sea animals have two big jobs. They need to find animals as food, and they have to try not to become other animal's meal.",questions:[{question:"People want to dive in the sea because they want to find the secrets of the undersea world.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"In the daytime, when you dive in the sea, you can see everything green and blue. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Animals will meet four types of danger under the deep sea. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"When you do scuba diving, you can dive freely without any danger. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"At the depth of 3,000 feet under the sea, all animals can find their way with the help of eyes.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Three man traveling on a train began a conversation about the world\'s greatest wonders.\n"In my opinion," the first man said, "the Egyptian pyramids" are the world\'s greatest wonder. Although they were built thousands of years ago, they are still standing. And remember: the people who built them had only simple tools. They did not have the kind of machinery that builders and engineers have today."\n" I agree that the pyramids in Egypt are wonderful," the second man said," But I don\'t think they are the greatest wonder. I believe computers are more wonderful than the pyramids. They are taken people to the moon and brought them back safely. In seconds, they carry out mathematical calculations that would take a person a hundred years to do."\nHe turned to the third man and asked, "What do you think is the greatest wonder in world?"\nThe third man thought for a long time, and then he said, "Well, I agree that the pyramids are wonderful, and I agree that computers are wonderful, too. However, in my opinion, the most wonderful thing in the world is this thermos."\nAnd he took a thermos out of his bag and held it up.\nThe other two men were very surprised. "A thermos?" they exclaimed. "But that\'s a simple thing."\n"Oh, no, it\'s not," the third man said. "In the winter you put in a hot drink and it says hot. In the summer you put in a cold drink and it stays cold. How does the thermos know whether it\'s winter or summer?"\n',questions:[{question:'The underlined word "thermos" in Chinese means ',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"That the three men could not agree on what the world's greatest wonder was because they all had different ideas. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The first man thought the pyramids were the most wonderful things in the world because they had been built with very simple tools. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The third man thought a thermos was the most wonderful thing in the world because it cost less than a computer. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The third man was not very clever because he could not think of anything to say.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]}],u=[{text:"     More and more teachers and parents have noticed another kind of pollution, which came from the printed papers sold on streets.\n  There printed things look like newspaper but have hardly anything to do with them. You can only find reading material badly ___1___ there- some are too strange for anyone to believe, ___2___ are frightening stories of something even worse. However, many of the young students are getting absorbed in such poisonous reading, which costs them what they should pay for their breakfast and bring them nightmares and immoral ideas in return. Homework is left undone, daily games lost. \n  There sellers shout on streets selling their papers well. The writers, publishers and printers, ___3___ they are, we never know, are making their silent money. They sheep skinned wolf's stories seem to have been forgotten once again.\n  Why not forbid this kind of things at school?  Yes, both teachers and parents have asked each other for more strict control of the young readers. Yet unfortunately, ___4___ you want to forbid it, the more they want to have a look at it sometimes you may even find several children share one patched paper, which has travelled from one hand to another driven by the curious nature.\n   It really does harm to our society. It has already formed a sort of moral pollution. The ___5___teachers and parents need more powerful support. Meanwhile, the young readers need more interesting books to help them get rid of these ugly papers.",questions:[{options:["others\t\t","made up\t\t","worried\t ","whoever\t\t","the more"],answer:"B"},{options:["others\t\t","made up\t\t","worried\t ","whoever\t\t","the more"],answer:"A"},{options:["others\t\t","made up\t\t","worried\t ","whoever\t\t","the more"],answer:"D"},{options:["others\t\t","made up\t\t","worried\t ","whoever\t\t","the more"],answer:"E"},{options:["others\t\t","made up\t\t","worried\t ","whoever\t\t","the more"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"    One of the latest imports is acupuncture (针刺疗法), the use of needles for ___1 ___ disease. Although acupuncture has been practiced in China for 2000 years, it's ___2___ in the Western world is still very ___3___. Several hospitals in the United States are now experimenting with acupuncture as a way of treating pains.\n  An American journalist descried the process ___4 ___ its effects. To keep the patient ___5___ feeling pain during the operation, four needles were used, each about an inch and a half long. The tops of the needles were attached to wires which led to a small electrical device. ",questions:[{options:["and    \t","treating\t   ","from   ","new\t ","use"],answer:"B"},{options:["and    \t","treating\t   ","from   ","new\t ","use"],answer:"E"},{options:["and    \t","treating\t   ","from   ","new\t ","use"],answer:"D"},{options:["and    \t","treating\t   ","from   ","new\t ","use"],answer:"A"},{options:["and    \t","treating\t   ","from   ","new\t ","use"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"Eagle has the longest life-span of its species. Eagle can ___1___ up to 70 years, but to reach this age eagle must make a hard decision.\n  In it's 40's, its long and flexible talons (爪) can no longer grab prey(掠食) which serves as food, its long and sharp beak (鸟嘴,喙) become bent. Its old-aged and heavy wings, due to their thick feathers, become stuck to its chest and make it ___2___ to fly. Then , the eagle is left with only two options: die or go through a painful process of change which lasts 150 days for survival.\n  The process requires that eagle fly to a mountain top and sit on its nest. There the eagle knocks its beak ___3___ a rock until it plucks (拔去)it out. After plucking it out, eagle will wait for a new beak to grow back. When its new talons grow back the eagles starts plucking its old-aged feathers and after five months, eagle an take its flight of rebirth and live for thirty ___4___years.\n  Many times, in order to survive, we have to start a change process. We sometimes need to ___5___ old memories, habits and other past traditions. Only freed from past burdens, can we take advantage of the present.",questions:[{options:["against   \t","difficult\t    ","get rid of    ","live   ","more"],answer:"D"},{options:["against   \t","difficult\t    ","get rid of    ","live   ","more"],answer:"B"},{options:["against   \t","difficult\t    ","get rid of    ","live   ","more"],answer:"A"},{options:["against   \t","difficult\t    ","get rid of    ","live   ","more"],answer:"E"},{options:["against   \t","difficult\t    ","get rid of    ","live   ","more"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"It's always interesting to visit another country, especially for those who have never travelled a great deal. Foreign ___1___can be very educational for anyone if he is interested enough to make preparations beforehand. Learning the language of the new country would be difficult for the traveller, ___2___ the benefits of such an effort would become obvious immediately on his arrival. It may not seem important to him when he comfortably stay at home, but knowing how to order a meal or book a room is necessary for the newcomer in a strange country. Without knowing the language, it's very difficult ___3___ the stranger to understand the people of the new country and their customs.\n  Of course, in our small world it is often possible to find someone who understands our own, but this is only second-best for the traveller. To be sure, he can see places and things without the use of a language, but places and things ___4___ not the heart of any country. To get the greatest benefit from a trip ___5___ another country, it is how important for the visitor to have an understanding of the language.",questions:[{options:["travel   \t","are\t    ","for    ","but   ","to"],answer:"A"},{options:["travel   \t","are\t    ","for    ","but   ","to"],answer:"D"},{options:["travel   \t","are\t    ","for    ","but   ","to"],answer:"C"},{options:["travel   \t","are\t    ","for    ","but   ","to"],answer:"B"},{options:["travel   \t","are\t    ","for    ","but   ","to"],answer:"E"}]},{text:'    A little boy wanted to meet God, so he started his trip with some cakes and orange juice. On his way he saw an old woman __1__ in the park. The boy sat down next to her. The old lady looked hungry, so he offered her a cake. She accepted it thankfully and smiled at him. Her smile was __2__ pretty that the boy wanted to see it again, so he gave her a bottle of orange juice. Once again she smiled at him. The boy was very happy! They sat there all afternoon eating and smiling, but they never say a word. As it grew dark, the boy got up to leave. __3__ he left, he gave her a kiss. She gave him her biggest smile ever. \n  When the boy got home, his mother saw the look of joy on his face. She asked him, "__4__ made you so happy?" He replied, " I had lunch with God. She\'s got the most beautiful smile I\'ve ever seen!" The old woman also returned to her home __5__. Her son asked, "Mother, why are you so happy?" She answered, "I ate cakes in the park with God. You know, he\'s much younger than I expected.\n      ',questions:[{options:["so   ","What    ","sitting     ","happily     ","Before"],answer:"C"},{options:["so   ","What    ","sitting     ","happily     ","Before"],answer:"A"},{options:["so   ","What    ","sitting     ","happily     ","Before"],answer:"E"},{options:["so   ","What    ","sitting     ","happily     ","Before"],answer:"B"},{options:["so   ","What    ","sitting     ","happily     ","Before"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'One day a woman got into her car and start driving home after work. Suddeny, she saw a yellow car behind her. The driver was a man. When she turned left, the yellow car turned left. When she turned right, the yellow car turned right, ___1 ___. When she stopped at the traffic lights, the yellow car stopped ___2 ___her. The woman was afraid, so she drove quickly to the police station. She was very surprised when she found the car stopped behind her. At that time, a young man was standing outside the police station. The woman was very happy to see him. She knew that he was a policeman because he was ___3 ___ a police uniform. She jumped out of her car and ran to the policeman. She asked him to arrest the man in the yellow car, so the policeman walked to the man. \n  The man didn\'t try to run ___4___ when he saw the policeman. He just smiled and said to the woman, "I want to give this purse back to you, madam. I think you ___5___ it on the street." ',questions:[{options:["wearing   \t","behind\t   ","too\t   ","dropped\t\t","Away"],answer:"C"},{options:["wearing   \t","behind\t   ","too\t   ","dropped\t\t","Away"],answer:"B"},{options:["wearing   \t","behind\t   ","too\t   ","dropped\t\t","Away"],answer:"A"},{options:["wearing   \t","behind\t   ","too\t   ","dropped\t\t","Away"],answer:"E"},{options:["wearing   \t","behind\t   ","too\t   ","dropped\t\t","Away"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"  Did you sleep well last night? Maybe people will answer. No. in fact, in the world about one in three people don't have good sleep. ___1___ you say you do not have good sleep, it means waking early and not getting back to sleep, often interrupted short period of sleep, or hours of wakefulness. You ___2___ get tired, worried, and anxious. Your memory and ability to remember things will be affected.\n  Then what should you do when you have the trouble?Do not worry about it too much. First, let's see whether you can sleep yourself. The ways are as follows:\n  First ___3___ that you bedroom isn't too cold or too hot. Keep it dark and quiet.\n  Second, check your lifestyle:\n  Do not drink tea, coffee, cola or chocolate four hours before going to bed. Drink less liquid so that you can have no or less visits to the toilet.\n  Set your body clock well by getting up and going to bed at the fixed time every day. You ___4___take and daytime naps. \n  Develop a relaxing bedtime habit. Read or listen to music, then take a warm bath. If you really can not sleep, try some bread, rice or milk . They will help you fast asleep.\n  Go for a daily walk. Natural light helps you to put your body clock into correct habit, ___5___do exercise outdoor if you can.\n  Forget the worries of the day, write down any worries, thoughts or questions before you go to bed. With these written down, you will have less to think about and your sleep will become easier. ",questions:[{options:["make sure\t\t","may\t\t","if\t    ","had better not \t","so"],answer:"C"},{options:["make sure\t\t","may\t\t","if\t    ","had better not \t","so"],answer:"B"},{options:["make sure\t\t","may\t\t","if\t    ","had better not \t","so"],answer:"A"},{options:["make sure\t\t","may\t\t","if\t    ","had better not \t","so"],answer:"D"},{options:["make sure\t\t","may\t\t","if\t    ","had better not \t","so"],answer:"E"}]},{text:"Without time to relax and have fine, kids can suffer stress just like adults, warn exports-who say as many as one in four youngsters have symptoms of burnout (过度劳累). More and more parents are pushing the kids to be busy in structured activities all the time. Many of these activities for children aren't recreational (娱乐的) ___1___involve competition. The kids are pushed to win, not just participate, and this can cause stress. Today's parents have the ___2___ that children who don't pursue a lot of outside activities will be left behind. Parents are in a panic because they know it's ___3___world out there. They are running scared to be sure their kids can go into the marketplace and compete as adults, but ___4___ some cases they are missing the big picture.\n  Kids who are unhappy and depressed grow up to the unhappy, depressed adults who don't do well in their jobs or personal life . And these kids won't know as adults how to relax. Everyone needs time just to relax and refresh. When you're not stressed, you can be ___5___ productive. That's why it's important to help your child find a balance.",questions:[{options:["in\t\t","idea\t\t","but\t       ","more\t","tough"],answer:"C"},{options:["in\t\t","idea\t\t","but\t       ","more\t","tough"],answer:"B"},{options:["in\t\t","idea\t\t","but\t       ","more\t","tough"],answer:"E"},{options:["in\t\t","idea\t\t","but\t       ","more\t","tough"],answer:"A"},{options:["in\t\t","idea\t\t","but\t       ","more\t","tough"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"Many students find the experience of attending university lectures to be a confusing and frustrating experience. The lecturer speaks for one or two hours, perhaps ____1__ the talk with slides,writing up important information on the blackboard, distributing reading material and giving out assignment. The new student sees the other students continuously writing on notebooks and ___2___ what to write. Very often the student leaves the lecture with notes which do not catch the main points and which become hard even for the students to understand. \n  Most institutions provide courses which assist new students to develop the skills they need to be effective listeners and note-takers. If these are unavailable, there are many useful study-skills guides which __3____ learners to practice these skills independently. In all cases it is important to __4___ the problem before actually starting your studies. \n  It is important to acknowledge that most students have difficulty in acquiring the language skills required in college study. One way of ___5___ these difficulties is to attend the language and study-skills classes which most institutions provide throughout the academic year. Another basic strategy is to find a study partner with whom it is possible to identify difficulties,exchange ideas and provide support. ",questions:[{options:["which \t","enable \t","overcoming    ","trackle\t  ","illustrating"],answer:"E"},{options:["which \t","enable \t","overcoming    ","trackle\t  ","illustrating"],answer:"A"},{options:["which \t","enable \t","overcoming    ","trackle\t  ","illustrating"],answer:"B"},{options:["which \t","enable \t","overcoming    ","trackle\t  ","illustrating"],answer:"D"},{options:["which \t","enable \t","overcoming    ","trackle\t  ","illustrating"],answer:"C"}]},{text:'There was a woman in Detroit, who had two sons. She was worried about them, especially the younger one, Ben, because he was not doing well in school. Boys in his class made jokes about him because he seemed so __1__.\n      The mother decided that she would herself have to get her sons to do better in school. She told them to go to the Detroit Public Library to read a book a week and do a book report for her.\n      One day, in Ben\'s __2__, the teacher held up a rock and asked if anyone knew it. Ben put up his hand and the teacher let him __3__. "Why did Ben put up his hand?" his classmates wondered. "He never said anything. What could he possibly want to say?"\n  Well, Ben not only __4__ the rock, but also said a lot about it. He named other rocks in its group and even knew where the teacher had found it. The teacher and the students were surprised. Ben had learned all this from doing one of his book reports.\n  Ben later went on to the __5__ of his class. When he finished high school, he went to Yale University and at last became one of the best doctors in the United States.',questions:[{options:["top    ","slow    ","class    ","answer    ","knew"],answer:"B"},{options:["top    ","slow    ","class    ","answer    ","knew"],answer:"C"},{options:["top    ","slow    ","class    ","answer    ","knew"],answer:"D"},{options:["top    ","slow    ","class    ","answer    ","knew"],answer:"E"},{options:["top    ","slow    ","class    ","answer    ","knew"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"In the eighteenth century, cities became larger and larger. People moved from the countryside and small towns to the __1__ because there was more work for them to do in the cities.\n  On Sundays and holidays, they liked to leave the cities and have a good time in the countryside. But not every __2__had a horse or a wagon(四轮马车). People needed a simpler means of transportation. Inventors in many countries tied to solve this problem.\n  The first bicycle, which is very simple, __3__ in 1790. People called \"the horse on wheel\". Then in 1861, after many improvements being made, the bicycle became a practical __4__ of transportation.\n  People liked bikes because they weren't as expensive as horses and didn't need to be fed. They could go anywhere and were easy to __5__.",questions:[{options:["appeared     ","cities    ","family    ","means    ","ride"],answer:"B"},{options:["appeared     ","cities    ","family    ","means    ","ride"],answer:"C"},{options:["appeared     ","cities    ","family    ","means    ","ride"],answer:"A"},{options:["appeared     ","cities    ","family    ","means    ","ride"],answer:"D"},{options:["appeared     ","cities    ","family    ","means    ","ride"],answer:"E"}]},{text:"Man has always wanted to fly. Even as long as eight hundred years ago, an Englishman had tried. He made a pair of __1__ from chicken feathers and fixed them to his shoulders. Then he jumped from a tall building. As you can imagine, he did not fly very far. __2__, the fell to the ground and broke several bones. The first real attempt at flying took place in France in 1783. The two Mongolian brothers knew that hot air rose. If they could fill a large balloon with hot air, they thought it would rise into the air and __3__. They were right. They made a very large hot air balloon of cloth and paper. It measured ten meters in diameter. They filled it with hot air and the balloon got two hundred meters into the air. It fell to earth about three kilometers __4__.\n  At the next attempt, they arranged for a balloon to carry passengers. We do not know what the passengers felt about the trip as they were a cock, a duck, and a sheep. But we __5__ know that the trip lasted eight minutes and the animals landed safely. ",questions:[{options:["Instead     ","wings    ","do   ","away    ","Fly"],answer:"B"},{options:["Instead     ","wings    ","do   ","away    ","Fly"],answer:"A"},{options:["Instead     ","wings    ","do   ","away    ","Fly"],answer:"E"},{options:["Instead     ","wings    ","do   ","away    ","Fly"],answer:"D"},{options:["Instead     ","wings    ","do   ","away    ","Fly"],answer:"C"}]},{text:'"Mom, can I have some money?" those are the words my mother used to hear all the time. In return, I heard, "why don\'t you get a job? Not to make the happy, but so that you have your own money and gain a bit more responsibility." So last year I got a job working about 25 hours a week. For $5 an hour, working as a salesman in a photo studio.\n  After I got this __1__, I had to do football, homework and job at the same time. It was really hard for me. I was burning out, falling asleep at school and failing __2__ many courses. My teachers were mad at me and yelled at me: why have a job? I missed a lot practice in football team and could only __3__back down at the match. My coach was cold at me with an unasked question: why have a job? I told them is was for the things I need, when actually it was or the things I wanted. Needing and wanting are different. Needing something is like your only shoes have holes in them. But wanting  us have every new brand sneaker just because you __4__ it. I start to think about if I did a wrong thing. Slowly, I learnt to manage my money better so that I could have more time for school and football. I learnt t make a wide __5__ on what I need and what I want.',questions:[{options:["decision    ","like   ","sit   ","in   ","Job"],answer:"E"},{options:["decision    ","like   ","sit   ","in   ","Job"],answer:"D"},{options:["decision    ","like   ","sit   ","in   ","Job"],answer:"C"},{options:["decision    ","like   ","sit   ","in   ","Job"],answer:"B"},{options:["decision    ","like   ","sit   ","in   ","Job"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Memory is very important in our life. A good memory is great help for learning a language. Everybody learns __1__ own language by keeping in mind what he hears when he is small child. Some children like those who __2__ abroad with their __3__, seem to learn two languages easily as they do one. In school, it's not easy for pupils __4__ a second language because they have very __5__time for it. Memory is like a diary that we keep every day.\n  ",questions:[{options:["live    ","little    ","parents   ","his   ","to learn"],answer:"D"},{options:["live    ","little    ","parents   ","his   ","to learn"],answer:"A"},{options:["live    ","little    ","parents   ","his   ","to learn"],answer:"C"},{options:["live    ","little    ","parents   ","his   ","to learn"],answer:"E"},{options:["live    ","little    ","parents   ","his   ","to learn"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Many people would agree that stress is a major problem in modern life. It is certainly true that worry and quarrel can cause all kinds of illnesses, __1__ backache to severe headaches, or even more serious complaints such as high blood pressure.\n  Many of us think __2__ stress as something that other people impose on us. We often complain about how other people put us __3__ pressure. But we should try not to let such pressure affect us. We should not forget that we are largely responsible for some of the stress ourselves. We sometimes take __4__ more work than our bodies and our minds can handle. We should learn to __5__ our limitations. We should be aware of which things are really important and which are not.",questions:[{options:["of\t\t","under\t","accept\t    ","from\t","on"],answer:"D"},{options:["of\t\t","under\t","accept\t    ","from\t","on"],answer:"A"},{options:["of\t\t","under\t","accept\t    ","from\t","on"],answer:"B"},{options:["of\t\t","under\t","accept\t    ","from\t","on"],answer:"E"},{options:["of\t\t","under\t","accept\t    ","from\t","on"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"Last night, a fire broke out in Ann's house in Manchester.\n  Ann's parents were out of town for the weekend when something wrong in the room caused the fire to __1__ in the middle of the night. The girl was waken up by the family dog, Danny, who was barking loudly in the back garden. Ann smelled something __2__. She got up and once ran through the smoke-filled house to wake her old brother, Frank.\n  When Frank would not wake up, Ann got some help from the dog. Frank's unconscious body was far too __3__ for the little girl to more alone, but the clever girl brought the dog inside and __4__ the dog's leash (牵狗的皮带)to Frank's left ankle. She then held her brother's right ankle, and together the girl and the dog __5__ Frank to safety. \n  The 10-years old girl, Ann, saved her big brothers from death. ",questions:[{options:["heavy\t\t","burning\t","start    ","pulled\t","tied"],answer:"C"},{options:["heavy\t\t","burning\t","start    ","pulled\t","tied"],answer:"B"},{options:["heavy\t\t","burning\t","start    ","pulled\t","tied"],answer:"A"},{options:["heavy\t\t","burning\t","start    ","pulled\t","tied"],answer:"E"},{options:["heavy\t\t","burning\t","start    ","pulled\t","tied"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"Modern zoos are very different from zoos that were built fifty years ago. At that time, zoos were places ____1____ people could go to see animals from many parts of the world. The animals lived in cages that were made ____2____ concrete with iron bars, cages that were easy to keep clean. \n       Unfortunately for the animals, the cages were small and impossible to hide in. The zoo environment was anything but natural. ____3____ the zoo keepers took good care of the animals and fed them well, many of the animals did not thrive; they behaved in strange ways, and they often became ill.\n       In modern zoos, people can see animals in more natural habitats. The animals are given more ___4___in large areas so that they can live more comfortably as they would in nature. Even the appearance of zoos has changed. Trees and grass grow in the cages, and streams of water flow___5___the areas that animals live in.",questions:[{options:["of\t   ","Although\t","where\t","over\t\t","freedom"],answer:"C"},{options:["of\t   ","Although\t","where\t","over\t\t","freedom"],answer:"A"},{options:["of\t   ","Although\t","where\t","over\t\t","freedom"],answer:"B"},{options:["of\t   ","Although\t","where\t","over\t\t","freedom"],answer:"E"},{options:["of\t   ","Although\t","where\t","over\t\t","freedom"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'Three men came to London for a holiday. They came to a large hotel and took a room there. ___1___ room was on the fiftieth floor.\n  In the evening the three men went to a cinema and came back very ___2___.\n  "I\'m sorry," said the assistant of the hotel. "Our lifts are not working at this time of night. If you don\'t want to walk up to your room, we shall make up a bed for you in the hall."\n  "No, no," Tom, one of the three men, said, "No, thank you. We do not want to sleep in the hall. We shall walk up to our room."\n  Then he turned to his two friends and said, "It is not easy to walk up to the fiftieth floor, but I know ___3___make it easier. On our way to the room, I shall tell you some jokes, then you, Andy, sing us some songs, then you, Peter, tell us some interesting stories."\n  "All right. That\'s a good idea," the friends both agreed.\n  They began to walk up to their room. Tom told many jokes. Andy sang some songs. ___4___ they came to the thirty-eighth floor. They were tired and decided to have a rest.\n  "Well," said Tom, "Now it\'s your turn, Peter. After all those jokes and songs, tell us a long and interesting story with a sad ending." "All right," said Peter, "I shall tell you a story. It is not long, ___5___ it is really sad: We left the key in our room in the hall."',questions:[{options:["At last\t\t","late\t\t","Their       ","but\t   ","how to"],answer:"C"},{options:["At last\t\t","late\t\t","Their       ","but\t   ","how to"],answer:"B"},{options:["At last\t\t","late\t\t","Their       ","but\t   ","how to"],answer:"E"},{options:["At last\t\t","late\t\t","Their       ","but\t   ","how to"],answer:"A"},{options:["At last\t\t","late\t\t","Their       ","but\t   ","how to"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'It\'s very interesting to stud names of different countries. Chinese names are different __1__ foreign names. Once an English lady came to visit me. When I was introduced to her, she said "Glad to meet you, Miss Ping." Then she gave her name card with three words on it "Betty J.Black". So I said "Thank you, Miss Betty." We looked at each other and laughed heartily. Later I found that the English people __2__ their family name last and the given name first, while their middles are not used very much. I explained to her that the Chinese family name comes first, the given name last, so she __3__ never call me Miss Ping. She asked if we Chinese had a middle name. I told her we didn\'t. But people may often find three words on a Chinese name card. In this case the family name still comes first and the other two words after it __4__ a two-word given name. It is quite usual in China. My sister is Li Xiaofang. She has two words in her given name instead __5__ just one like mine.',questions:[{options:["put\t\t","from\t\t","should      ","of\t   ","are"],answer:"B"},{options:["put\t\t","from\t\t","should      ","of\t   ","are"],answer:"A"},{options:["put\t\t","from\t\t","should      ","of\t   ","are"],answer:"C"},{options:["put\t\t","from\t\t","should      ","of\t   ","are"],answer:"E"},{options:["put\t\t","from\t\t","should      ","of\t   ","are"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"The world is not only hungry; it is also thirsty for water. This may seem strange to you, since nearly 75% of the earth's surface is covered with water. But about 97% of this huge____1____is seawater, or salt water. Man can only drink and use the other 3% of the fresh water that comes from rivers, lakes, underground, and other____2____. And we can't even use all of that, because some of it is in the form of icebergs and glaciers. Even worse, some of it has been polluted. However, as things stand today, this small amount of fresh water,____3____is constantly being replaced by rainfall; is still enough for us. But our need for water is increasing rapidly-almost day by day. We all have to learn how to stop wasting our ____4____ water. One of the first steps we should take is to develop ways of reusing it. Experiments have already been done in this ____5____, but only on a small scale. The systems that have been worked out resemble those used in spacecraft.",questions:[{options:["field     ","sources  ","which  ","precious  ","amount "],answer:"E"},{options:["field     ","sources  ","which  ","precious  ","amount "],answer:"B"},{options:["field     ","sources  ","which  ","precious  ","amount "],answer:"C"},{options:["field     ","sources  ","which  ","precious  ","amount "],answer:"D"},{options:["field     ","sources  ","which  ","precious  ","amount "],answer:"A"}]}];function w(e,t){var o=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var n=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(n=n.filter(function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable})),o.push.apply(o,n)}return o}function c(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var o=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?w(o,!0).forEach(function(t){Object(s["a"])(e,t,o[t])}):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(o)):w(o).forEach(function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(o,t))})}return e}var m={name:"english",data:function(){return{dxlist:[],wxlist:[],ydlist:[],A_Z:["A","B","C","D","E","F"],submit:!1,score:0,meta:null}},methods:{getDanXuan:function(){var e=[].concat(Object(i["a"])(h),[r]);this.dxlist=[];for(var t=0;t<10;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.dxlist.push(c({},e[o],{xx:""})),e.splice(o,1)}},getYueDu:function(){var e=[].concat(Object(i["a"])(l),Object(i["a"])(d));this.ydlist=[];for(var t=0;t<4;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.ydlist.push({text:e[o].text,questions:e[o].questions.map(function(e){return c({},e,{xx:""})})}),e.splice(o,1)}},getWanXing:function(){var e=Object(i["a"])(u);this.wxlist=[];for(var t=0;t<2;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.wxlist.push({text:e[o].text,questions:e[o].questions.map(function(e){return c({},e,{xx:""})})}),e.splice(o,1)}},submitFn:function(){var e=this;this.score=0,this.dxlist.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)}),this.wxlist.forEach(function(t){t.questions.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)})}),this.ydlist.forEach(function(t){t.questions.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)})}),this.submit=!0},reset:function(){this.score=0,this.submit=!1,this.getDanXuan(),this.getWanXing(),this.getYueDu()}},mounted:function(){this.m=document.createElement("meta"),this.m.name="viewport",this.m.content="user-scalable=no, initial-scale=1, maximum-scale=1, minimum-scale=1, width=device-width, viewport-fit=cover",document.getElementsByTagName("head")[0].appendChild(this.m);var e=window.innerWidth||document.body.clientWidth||document.documentElement.clientWidth,t=e/750;t>1&&this.$router.replace("/english"),t=t>1?1:t<.427?.427:t,document.getElementsByTagName("html")[0].style.fontSize=100*t+"px"},beforeDestroy:function(){document.getElementsByTagName("head")[0].removeChild(this.m)},created:function(){this.getDanXuan(),this.getWanXing(),this.getYueDu()}},p=m,f=(o("ff0c"),o("2877")),y=Object(f["a"])(p,n,a,!1,null,"3cabe689",null);t["default"]=y.exports},3702:function(e,t,o){var n=o("481b"),a=o("5168")("iterator"),s=Array.prototype;e.exports=function(e){return void 0!==e&&(n.Array===e||s[a]===e)}},"40c3":function(e,t,o){var n=o("6b4c"),a=o("5168")("toStringTag"),s="Arguments"==n(function(){return arguments}()),i=function(e,t){try{return e[t]}catch(o){}};e.exports=function(e){var t,o,r;return void 0===e?"Undefined":null===e?"Null":"string"==typeof(o=i(t=Object(e),a))?o:s?n(t):"Object"==(r=n(t))&&"function"==typeof t.callee?"Arguments":r}},"454f":function(e,t,o){o("46a7");var n=o("584a").Object;e.exports=function(e,t,o){return n.defineProperty(e,t,o)}},"456d":function(e,t,o){var n=o("4bf8"),a=o("0d58");o("5eda")("keys",function(){return function(e){return a(n(e))}})},"46a7":function(e,t,o){var n=o("63b6");n(n.S+n.F*!o("8e60"),"Object",{defineProperty:o("d9f6").f})},"4ee1":function(e,t,o){var n=o("5168")("iterator"),a=!1;try{var s=[7][n]();s["return"]=function(){a=!0},Array.from(s,function(){throw 2})}catch(i){}e.exports=function(e,t){if(!t&&!a)return!1;var o=!1;try{var s=[7],r=s[n]();r.next=function(){return{done:o=!0}},s[n]=function(){return r},e(s)}catch(i){}return o}},"549b":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("d864"),a=o("63b6"),s=o("241e"),i=o("b0dc"),r=o("3702"),h=o("b447"),l=o("20fd"),d=o("7cd6");a(a.S+a.F*!o("4ee1")(function(e){Array.from(e)}),"Array",{from:function(e){var t,o,a,u,w=s(e),c="function"==typeof this?this:Array,m=arguments.length,p=m>1?arguments[1]:void 0,f=void 0!==p,y=0,g=d(w);if(f&&(p=n(p,m>2?arguments[2]:void 0,2)),void 0==g||c==Array&&r(g))for(t=h(w.length),o=new c(t);t>y;y++)l(o,y,f?p(w[y],y):w[y]);else for(u=g.call(w),o=new c;!(a=u.next()).done;y++)l(o,y,f?i(u,p,[a.value,y],!0):a.value);return o.length=y,o}})},"54a1":function(e,t,o){o("6c1c"),o("1654"),e.exports=o("95d5")},"5eda":function(e,t,o){var n=o("5ca1"),a=o("8378"),s=o("79e5");e.exports=function(e,t){var o=(a.Object||{})[e]||Object[e],i={};i[e]=t(o),n(n.S+n.F*s(function(){o(1)}),"Object",i)}},"75fc":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("a745"),a=o.n(n);function s(e){if(a()(e)){for(var t=0,o=new Array(e.length);t<e.length;t++)o[t]=e[t];return o}}var i=o("774e"),r=o.n(i),h=o("c8bb"),l=o.n(h);function d(e){if(l()(Object(e))||"[object Arguments]"===Object.prototype.toString.call(e))return r()(e)}function u(){throw new TypeError("Invalid attempt to spread non-iterable instance")}function w(e){return s(e)||d(e)||u()}o.d(t,"a",function(){return w})},"774e":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("d2d5")},"7cd6":function(e,t,o){var n=o("40c3"),a=o("5168")("iterator"),s=o("481b");e.exports=o("584a").getIteratorMethod=function(e){if(void 0!=e)return e[a]||e["@@iterator"]||s[n(e)]}},"85f2":function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("454f")},"8e6e":function(e,t,o){var n=o("5ca1"),a=o("990b"),s=o("6821"),i=o("11e9"),r=o("f1ae");n(n.S,"Object",{getOwnPropertyDescriptors:function(e){var t,o,n=s(e),h=i.f,l=a(n),d={},u=0;while(l.length>u)o=h(n,t=l[u++]),void 0!==o&&r(d,t,o);return d}})},9093:function(e,t,o){var n=o("ce10"),a=o("e11e").concat("length","prototype");t.f=Object.getOwnPropertyNames||function(e){return n(e,a)}},"95d5":function(e,t,o){var n=o("40c3"),a=o("5168")("iterator"),s=o("481b");e.exports=o("584a").isIterable=function(e){var t=Object(e);return void 0!==t[a]||"@@iterator"in t||s.hasOwnProperty(n(t))}},"990b":function(e,t,o){var n=o("9093"),a=o("2621"),s=o("cb7c"),i=o("7726").Reflect;e.exports=i&&i.ownKeys||function(e){var t=n.f(s(e)),o=a.f;return o?t.concat(o(e)):t}},a745:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("f410")},ac6a:function(e,t,o){for(var n=o("cadf"),a=o("0d58"),s=o("2aba"),i=o("7726"),r=o("32e9"),h=o("84f2"),l=o("2b4c"),d=l("iterator"),u=l("toStringTag"),w=h.Array,c={CSSRuleList:!0,CSSStyleDeclaration:!1,CSSValueList:!1,ClientRectList:!1,DOMRectList:!1,DOMStringList:!1,DOMTokenList:!0,DataTransferItemList:!1,FileList:!1,HTMLAllCollection:!1,HTMLCollection:!1,HTMLFormElement:!1,HTMLSelectElement:!1,MediaList:!0,MimeTypeArray:!1,NamedNodeMap:!1,NodeList:!0,PaintRequestList:!1,Plugin:!1,PluginArray:!1,SVGLengthList:!1,SVGNumberList:!1,SVGPathSegList:!1,SVGPointList:!1,SVGStringList:!1,SVGTransformList:!1,SourceBufferList:!1,StyleSheetList:!0,TextTrackCueList:!1,TextTrackList:!1,TouchList:!1},m=a(c),p=0;p<m.length;p++){var f,y=m[p],g=c[y],_=i[y],b=_&&_.prototype;if(b&&(b[d]||r(b,d,w),b[u]||r(b,u,y),h[y]=w,g))for(f in n)b[f]||s(b,f,n[f],!0)}},b0dc:function(e,t,o){var n=o("e4ae");e.exports=function(e,t,o,a){try{return a?t(n(o)[0],o[1]):t(o)}catch(i){var s=e["return"];throw void 0!==s&&n(s.call(e)),i}}},bd86:function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.d(t,"a",function(){return s});var n=o("85f2"),a=o.n(n);function s(e,t,o){return t in e?a()(e,t,{value:o,enumerable:!0,configurable:!0,writable:!0}):e[t]=o,e}},c8bb:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("54a1")},d2d5:function(e,t,o){o("1654"),o("549b"),e.exports=o("584a").Array.from},f1ae:function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("86cc"),a=o("4630");e.exports=function(e,t,o){t in e?n.f(e,t,a(0,o)):e[t]=o}},f410:function(e,t,o){o("1af6"),e.exports=o("584a").Array.isArray},ff0c:function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("154f"),a=o.n(n);a.a}}]);
//# sourceMappingURL=english-mobile-new.53ffc4b2.js.map